<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<yml_catalog date="2026-07-09 09:15:01">
  <shop>
    <name>lovelyus.com</name>
    <company>Lovely US</company>
    <url>https://lovelyus.com/</url>
    <currencies>
      <currency id="USD" rate="1"/>
    </currencies>
    <categories>
      <category id="1">Eye Patches</category>
      <category id="2">Eyelash Extension Adhesive</category>
      <category id="3">Eyelash Extensions</category>
      <category id="4">Eyelash Tweezers</category>
      <category id="5">Glue Bonder</category>
      <category id="6">Preparations</category>
      <category id="7">Related Materials</category>
    </categories>
    <offers>
      <offer id="9524033650965" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/lovelypro-hydrogel-eye-patches</url>
        <price>15</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>1</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/10_Pairs_Hydrogel_Eye_Patches.png?v=1778092727</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Patches.png?v=1778092748</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Packet_for_Patches.png?v=1778092764</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Hydrogel_Patches_on_a_Model.png?v=1778093117</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/30_Pairs_Box.png?v=1778092805</picture>
        <name>Hydrogel Eye Patches</name>
        <typePrefix>Eye Patches</typePrefix>
        <vendor>LovelyPro</vendor>
        <vendorCode>PATCH-10-PAIR</vendorCode>
        <description>LOVELYPRO. Hydrogel Eye Patches – 10 Pairs / 30 Pairs Professional Lint-Free Under Eye Pads for Eyelash Extension Application LOVELYPRO. is the professional-grade line by Lovely US, crafted exclusively for licensed lash artists who demand precision, comfort, and consistency in every service. The LOVELYPRO. Hydrogel Eye Patches are the under-eye essential every lash artist needs. Designed to gently secure lower lashes during eyelash extension application, these soft hydrogel pads are formulated to provide a cooling sensation and a moisturizing effect to the under-eye area — helping clients stay comfortable throughout the service. Why Hydrogel? Not all under-eye pads are created equal. Unlike foam pads or tape, hydrogel patches are designed to conform to the natural curve of the under-eye area, reducing gaps and improving lower lash coverage. The hydrogel formula contains water-binding ingredients that help maintain skin hydration during the service. Clients may notice a cooling, soothing sensation — making longer appointments more comfortable. Results may vary depending on skin type and individual sensitivity. Why Lash Artists Choose LovelyPro Hydrogel Eye Patches Soft, smooth &amp; gentle – Designed for comfort on sensitive skin 100% lint-free – No fibers to interfere with adhesive or lash placement Hydrogel formula – Helps maintain under-eye moisture during the service Cooling sensation – May help clients feel more relaxed during application Secure lower lash hold – Keeps lower lashes in place for cleaner, more precise work Flexible fit – Conforms to the under-eye contour for a consistent, non-slip grip Professional grade – Suitable for use in lash studios and salons Perfect For Classic, volume, and mega volume lash extension applications Lash artists who prioritize client comfort and skin safety Studios looking for a reliable, consistent under-eye pad Clients with sensitive or delicate under-eye skin How to Use Thoroughly clean and dry the under-eye area before application. Remove the patch from the liner. Apply the patch under the eye, securing lower lashes in place. Perform eyelash extension application as normal. After the service, remove the patch slowly from the edges. Ingredients Water (Aqua), Glycerin, Sodium Polyacrylate, Cellulose Gum, Polyvinylpyrrolidone (PVP), Aluminum Glycinate, Phenoxyethanol, Ethylhexylglycerin, Disodium EDTA, Tartaric Acid. Storage &amp; Safety Store in a cool, dry place away from direct sunlight and heat. For professional external use only. Do not use on broken, irritated, sunburned, or compromised skin. Avoid use if sensitive or allergic to bandages, adhesives, or peel-off masks. Avoid direct contact with eyes. If contact occurs, rinse with water. Discontinue use if redness, irritation, or discomfort occurs. Use immediately after opening. Do not reuse. Keep out of reach of children. Why Choose Lovely US We&apos;re one of the largest professional lash brands worldwide, trusted by over 5,000+ lash artists in North America and tens of thousands globally. Our products are carefully selected and tested to bring you the safest, highest-quality tools in the industry. We&apos;re committed to helping you enhance beauty wherever you are. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed – We stand behind the quality of every product we carry.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9524033650965</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eye Patches</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">accessories, hydrogel eye patches, lash extensions, lash supplies, under eye pads</param>
        <param name="Pairs" noFilter="true">10 Pairs, 30 Pairs</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">PATCH-10-PAIR, PATCH-30-PAIR</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">2</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9527850467605" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/final-selection-royal-eyelash-extensions-16-lines-l-curl-reduced-pricing</url>
        <price>8</price>
        <oldprice>17</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1384_56dad0c8-c170-4f5a-ba3a-9137f2252c37.jpg?v=1762457223</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9926_84740000-5ae6-4fd6-a255-8fbacedb9927.jpg?v=1615308486</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9929_010325da-0c58-4d03-9c2d-1f7de2da6079.jpg?v=1615308486</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart_49e8d02c-ca3d-4b97-be15-1f76b8ff0789.jpg?v=1615308486</picture>
        <name>Reduced Pricing | Royal Eyelash Extensions Tray- 16 Lines L Curl | 8mm-15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ROY-L-007-15</vendorCode>
        <description>Royal Eyelash Extensions - 16 Lines L Curl Achieve the perfect lifted look with our Royal L Curl Eyelash Extensions. Designed for professional lash technicians, this 16-line tray delivers natural-looking lift and opens the eye beautifully for clients with straight or downward-pointing natural lashes. L Curl Advantages Natural Lift Effect: L curl provides subtle elevation without appearing overly dramatic—ideal for clients seeking an everyday elegant look Straight Base Design: Flat base adheres perfectly to natural lashes, maximizing retention and bond strength Eye-Opening Results: Lifts and opens hooded or deep-set eyes while maintaining a soft, natural appearance Versatile Application: Works beautifully for classic, volume, and hybrid lash techniques Premium Fiber Quality: Maintains curl integrity and rich black color throughout wear What&apos;s Included In this 16 line tray there are up to 10,500 lashes depending on their thickness. Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Perfect For Clients with straight natural lashes, hooded eyes, or those who want a lifted look without extreme curl. The L curl is your go-to for natural lash lifts that photograph beautifully and feel weightless. Professional Features: 16 organized lines for efficient selection, consistent thickness across all lengths, easy-release adhesive strips for smooth pickup. Join thousands of lash artists who trust Royal Extensions for predictable, gorgeous results appointment after appointment.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9527850467605</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely US Lashes, Royal Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">L</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10, 0.12, 0.15, 0.18, 0.20</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">15mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ROY-L-007-15, ROY-L-010-8, ROY-L-010-9, ROY-L-010-10, ROY-L-010-11, ROY-L-010-12, ROY-L-010-13, ROY-L-010-14, ROY-L-010-15, ROY-L-012-8, ROY-L-012-9, ROY-L-012-10, ROY-L-012-11, ROY-L-012-12, ROY-L-012-13, ROY-L-012-14, ROY-L-012-15, ROY-L-015-8, ROY-L-015-9, ROY-L-015-10, +20 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">40</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9527065542933" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/final-selection-royal-eyelash-extensions-16-lines-reduced-pricing</url>
        <price>9</price>
        <oldprice>17</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1384_5fc43533-17e1-4ad1-aaef-faf70ffbfe14.jpg?v=1762457136</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9926.jpg?v=1603487854</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9929.jpg?v=1603487859</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart.jpg?v=1597504571</picture>
        <name>Reduced Pricing | Royal Eyelash Extensions Tray - 16 Lines | C, D | 7mm-16mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ROY-C-007-14</vendorCode>
        <description>Royal Eyelash Extensions - Professional 16 Line Tray Deliver flawless lash applications every time with our Royal Eyelash Extensions. This professional 16-line tray is the foundation of exceptional lash artistry, offering premium quality fibers that professional lash technicians depend on for stunning, long-lasting results. Professional-Grade Quality Consistent Perfection: Every lash maintains uniform thickness, taper, and curl for seamless application and beautiful symmetry Superior Retention: Advanced fiber technology ensures extensions stay put for 4-6 weeks with proper aftercare Rich Black Pigment: Deep, true black color eliminates the need for mascara and creates dramatic definition Lightweight Comfort: Ultra-fine construction feels natural and weightless on clients&apos; eyes Organized Efficiency: 16-line tray layout streamlines your workflow and reduces appointment time What&apos;s Included In this 16 line tray there are up to 10,500 lashes depending on their thickness. Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Versatile Application Ideal for classic lash sets, these extensions work beautifully across all eye shapes and natural lash types. Whether you&apos;re creating natural enhancement or bold glamour, Royal Extensions deliver the precision and quality your artistry deserves. Technical Excellence: Easy-release strips, consistent curl retention, flexible yet durable fibers, and professional-grade adhesion compatibility. Trusted by lash artists throughout North America. Stock your station with the extensions that elevate your reputation and keep clients loyal.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9527065542933</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely US Lashes, Royal Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10, 0.12, 0.15, 0.18, 0.20</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">14mm, 15mm, 16mm, 12mm, 13mm, 8mm, 9mm, 11mm, 10mm, 7mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ROY-C-007-14, ROY-C-007-15, ROY-C-007-16, ROY-C-010-12, ROY-C-010-13, ROY-C-010-14, ROY-C-010-15, ROY-C-010-16, ROY-C-012-8, ROY-C-012-9, ROY-C-012-11, ROY-C-012-12, ROY-C-012-13, ROY-C-012-14, ROY-C-012-15, ROY-C-015-8, ROY-C-015-9, ROY-C-015-12, ROY-C-015-13, ROY-C-015-14, +41 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">61</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9526476079381" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/final-selection-royal-eyelash-extensions-16-line-mix-reduced-pricing</url>
        <price>9</price>
        <oldprice>17</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1384_1ef5686b-9bbe-4d70-b104-20cdf9b893b5.jpg?v=1762457138</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9929_337eb243-71a9-41f7-adab-a4860c9f4a72.jpg?v=1603487928</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart_51852d11-bbe0-4d81-b2f4-b3d748f76909.jpg?v=1597504635</picture>
        <name>Reduced Pricing | Royal Eyelash Extensions Tray - 16 Line MIX | B, C, C+, CC, D, L, L+, M | 7-15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ROY-B-012-15</vendorCode>
        <description>Premium Royal Eyelash Extensions - 16 Line MIX Transform your lash artistry with our professional-grade Royal Eyelash Extensions. This 16-line mixed tray delivers exceptional versatility for creating customized, dimensional lash looks that keep clients coming back. Why Lash Artists Choose Royal Extensions Mixed Length Variety: Perfect assortment for volume and hybrid sets, allowing seamless blending and natural-to-dramatic styling Superior Retention: Premium synthetic fibers hold their curl and maintain flawless appearance for weeks Effortless Application: Consistent thickness and easy-release strips speed up your lash mapping process Professional Results: Deep black color creates bold, defined lashes without mascara 16 Organized Lines: Efficient tray layout keeps your workspace organized during appointments What&apos;s Included In this 16 line tray there are up to 10,500 lashes depending on their thickness. Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Technical Specifications Each tray contains carefully curated mixed lengths ideal for creating texture, dimension, and customized lash designs. The ultra-fine base ensures comfortable wear and invisible bonds. Perfect for: Volume sets, hybrid techniques, mega volume applications, and creative lash mapping Trusted by professional lash technicians across North America for consistent quality and reliable performance. Elevate every client&apos;s lash experience with Royal Extensions.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9526476079381</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Classic Eyelash Extensions, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, lashes, Royal Eyelash Extensions, Royal Lashes, Volume eyelash extensions</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">B, C, C+, CC, D, M, L, L+</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.12, 0.15, 0.18, 0.20</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">7-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ROY-B-012-15, ROY-B-015-15, ROY-B-018-15, ROY-B-020-15, ROY-C-012-15, ROY-C-015-15, ROY-C-018-15, ROY-C-020-15, ROY-C+-015-15, ROY-C+-018-15, ROY-C+-020-15, ROY-CC-012-15, ROY-CC-015-15, ROY-CC-018-15, ROY-CC-020-15, ROY-D-015-15, ROY-D-018-15, ROY-D-020-15, ROY-M-012-15, ROY-M-015-15, +10 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">30</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9525773959445" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/final-selection-ideal-lash-extensions-20-lines-reduced-price</url>
        <price>9</price>
        <oldprice>20</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_9fc40197-92fc-4b18-be4f-ac641eff76b7.jpg?v=1762457187</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_c8143654-e2c6-417d-8b62-8039bae8de03.jpg?v=1656021301</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart2.jpg?v=1656021272</picture>
        <name>Reduced Pricing | Ideal Lash Extensions 20 Lines Tray | C-D Curl | 8-16mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEL-C-007-15</vendorCode>
        <description>Classic 20 Line Eyelash Extensions for Professional Lash Artists Elevate your lash artistry with our Ideal Eyelash Extensions - 20 Lines , the foundation of every professional lash artist&apos;s toolkit. Designed for consistent, beautiful results across all lash techniques. Why Professionals Trust Ideal Extensions 20 Lines of Premium Lashes: Full professional tray with up to 13,000 high-quality extensions for multiple client applications Versatile Curl Options: Available in multiple curl types to suit every client&apos;s eye shape and desired look Superior Quality Fibers: Soft, lightweight synthetic lashes with a natural matte finish and excellent retention Consistent Performance: Reliable curl memory and flexibility for seamless application every time Multi-Technique Ready: Perfect for classic sets, hybrid designs, and volume fan creation Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Professional-Grade Quality Each lash is precision-manufactured to meet the exacting standards of professional lash technicians. From natural everyday looks to dramatic evening styles, these extensions deliver flawless results that keep clients satisfied. The professional standard for lash extensions. Build your reputation on quality that performs appointment after appointment.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9525773959445</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, Ideal lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10, 0.12, 0.15, 0.18, 0.20</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">15mm, 16mm, 14mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEL-C-007-15, IDEL-C-007-16, IDEL-C-010-14, IDEL-C-010-15, IDEL-C-010-16, IDEL-C-012-8, IDEL-C-012-9, IDEL-C-012-10, IDEL-C-012-11, IDEL-C-012-12, IDEL-C-012-13, IDEL-C-012-14, IDEL-C-012-15, IDEL-C-015-8, IDEL-C-015-9, IDEL-C-015-10, IDEL-C-015-11, IDEL-C-015-12, IDEL-C-015-13, IDEL-C-015-14, +49 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">69</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9525788737813" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/final-selection-ideal-eyelash-extensions-20-lines-cc-m-curl-reduced-price</url>
        <price>10</price>
        <oldprice>20</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_241d7837-327d-45a8-b75a-fa3896a2d9dd.jpg?v=1762457238</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_0d6e8387-c5d3-42e1-b5c6-00ab77e32726.jpg?v=1661909854</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart2_60169943-6758-44f0-9e54-e670dcf7c3f7.jpg?v=1661909854</picture>
        <name>Reduced Pricing | Ideal Eyelash Extensions Tray - 20 Lines CC/M Curl | 0.07-0.10 | 7mm-15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEL-CC-007-15</vendorCode>
        <description>Versatile CC/M Curl Eyelash Extensions for Natural to Dramatic Styles Discover the ultimate flexibility with our Ideal Eyelash Extensions in CC/M Curl – the go-to choice for lash professionals who create everything from natural everyday looks to glamorous volume sets. Premium Quality Features Ideal eyelash extensions are made of high-quality fiber, are very elastic and have a round basis on the cut. Ideal lashes have a soft natural shine and short tips. They are ideal for classic, hybrid, volume, and mega volume lashing. Why Professionals Love CC/M Curl Extensions Dual Curl Versatility: CC and M curls offer the perfect balance between natural lift and eye-opening drama, suitable for most eye shapes 20 Lines Per Tray: Professional-sized tray with up to 13,000 lashes for exceptional value and multiple client services Soft, Natural Appearance: Premium synthetic fibers with a subtle shine that looks beautiful and feels weightless Exceptional Retention: Engineered for superior bonding and long-lasting wear that keeps clients coming back Multi-Technique Compatible: Perfect for classic, hybrid, volume, and mega volume lash applications with consistent results Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Professional Quality You Can Trust Each lash is precision-crafted to maintain curl consistency and flexibility throughout the application process. Ideal for creating customized lash designs that enhance every client&apos;s natural beauty. Trusted by lash artists nationwide. Deliver stunning, reliable results with extensions designed for professional excellence.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9525788737813</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">CC curl lashes, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, hybrid lashes, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, Ideal lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lash artist supplies, lashes, Lovely Lashes, M curl lashes, professional extensions</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">CC, M</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">15mm, 7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEL-CC-007-15, IDEL-CC-010-07, IDEL-CC-010-08, IDEL-CC-010-09, IDEL-CC-010-10, IDEL-CC-010-11, IDEL-CC-010-12, IDEL-CC-010-13, IDEL-CC-010-14, IDEL-CC-010-15, IDEL-M-007-13, IDEL-M-007-14, IDEL-M-007-15, IDEL-M-010-09, IDEL-M-010-10, IDEL-M-010-11, IDEL-M-010-12, IDEL-M-010-13, IDEL-M-010-14, IDEL-M-010-15</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">20</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9525738963221" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/final-price-ideal-eyelash-extensions-20-line-mix</url>
        <price>9</price>
        <oldprice>20</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions.jpg?v=1762457187</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-0081.jpg?v=1603918528</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9829copy.jpg?v=1603489320</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart2_6ce817d9-f027-4cc5-a890-fd352cf3bc57.jpg?v=1597504806</picture>
        <name>Reduced Pricing | Ideal Lash Extensions 20 Line Mix | B C C+ CC D L L+ M | 7-15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEL-B-005-715</vendorCode>
        <description>Complete 20 Line Mix Eyelash Extensions for Every Lash Design Streamline your lash inventory with our Ideal Eyelash Extensions 20 Line Mix – the all-in-one solution for professional lash artists who need multiple lengths in one convenient tray. Why Lash Technicians Choose the 20 Line Mix Complete Length Range: Mixed lengths in one tray for creating seamless lash maps without switching between multiple trays 20 Lines of Variety: Professional assortment designed for maximum efficiency and creative flexibility Time-Saving Convenience: Everything you need for classic, hybrid, and volume sets in one organized tray Premium Quality Fibers: Soft, lightweight lashes with natural shine and superior retention Consistent Curl Pattern: Uniform curl across all lengths for predictable, beautiful results every time Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Perfect for Busy Lash Artists Designed to simplify your workflow while maintaining the highest quality standards. Create custom lash designs efficiently with all the lengths you need at your fingertips. Work smarter, not harder. The 20 Line Mix gives you professional versatility without the clutter of multiple trays.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9525738963221</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Classic Eyelash Extensions, Classic Lashes, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, Ideal Lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, lashes, Lovely US Lashes, Volume eyelash extensions, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">B, C, C+, CC, D, M, L, L+</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.05, 0.12, 0.15, 0.18, 0.20, 0.10, 0.07</param>
        <param name="Size" noFilter="true">7-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEL-B-005-715, IDEL-B-012-715, IDEL-B-015-715, IDEL-B-018-715, IDEL-B-020-715, IDEL-C-005-715, IDEL-C-012-715, IDEL-C-018-715, IDEL-C-020-715, IDEL-C+-015-715, IDEL-C+-018-715, IDEL-C+-020-715, IDEL-CC-010-715, IDEL-CC-012-715, IDEL-CC-015-715, IDEL-CC-018-715, IDEL-CC-020-715, IDEL-D-005-715, IDEL-D-015-715, IDEL-D-018-715, +16 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">36</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9355512807701" available="false">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/cleopatra-eyelash-extension-glue-copy</url>
        <price>35</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>2</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/ap09gxq0tl77tkmntj303vx2db1ehjdn.jpg?v=1765303920</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/4_81a39168-840c-457c-881c-f10483eab431.png?v=1761754894</picture>
        <name>Cleopatra Eyelash Extension Glue – Deep Black, 1-Second Dry, 8-Week Hold, 5 ml</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extension Adhesive</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>9355512807701</vendorCode>
        <description>Cleopatra Eyelash Extension Glue by Lovely US – 5 ml What is Cleopatra Lash Glue? Cleopatra Eyelash Extension Glue is a professional-grade, deep black lash adhesive manufactured by Lovely US in South Korea. It features a 1-second drying time , 8-week retention , smooth balanced viscosity , and a rich black pigment for a defined, dramatic lash line. It is compatible with both classic and volume eyelash extension techniques and is designed for experienced to expert lash technicians. Cleopatra is one of the most trusted adhesives in the Lovely US lineup , valued by professional lash artists for its consistent texture, reliable bonding, and deep black finish that enhances every lash set. Key Specifications Brand: Lovely US Volume: 5 ml Color: Deep black Drying time: 1 second Retention: Up to 8 weeks Viscosity: Smooth / balanced (minimal clumping) Pigment: Rich, deep black for dramatic definition Compatible techniques: Classic and volume eyelash extensions Skill level: Experienced to expert lash technicians Country of origin: South Korea Full Ingredient List Ethyl Cyanoacrylate, Methoxyethyl Cyanoacrylate, Polymethyl Methacrylate, CI 77266 Why Lash Artists Choose Cleopatra 1-second dry time — Optimal speed and precision for experienced lash artists who need reliable, fast curing 8-week retention — Long-lasting bond that reduces client fill frequency and increases satisfaction Deep black pigment — Rich, defined lash line for dramatic, high-contrast results on every set Smooth balanced viscosity — Consistent texture that prevents clumping and allows precise lash placement Versatile technique compatibility — Performs reliably across both classic and volume applications Trusted formula — One of the most reliable adhesives in the professional lash industry, refined over years of use Made in South Korea — Professional-grade, salon-safe formulation Optimal Working Conditions For consistent 1-second curing, maintain the following environment: Temperature: 64°F–75°F (18°C–24°C) Humidity: 40%–70% relative humidity Shelf life (unopened): 6 months from production date Shelf life (after opening): Use within 2 months for optimal performance How to Apply Cleopatra Lash Glue Shake the bottle horizontally for 30–60 seconds before use to ensure proper consistency Dispense a small drop onto a glue palette or jade stone Dip only the base of the lash extension into the adhesive Apply to the natural lash with precision for a secure bond Replace the glue drop every 10 minutes to maintain freshness and optimal curing speed Professional Tips for Best Results The horizontal shake technique is important for Cleopatra — it ensures the pigment and adhesive components are fully blended before dispensing The smooth, balanced viscosity makes Cleopatra especially well-suited for detailed placement on fine natural lashes without clumping Use a calibrated hygrometer to monitor room humidity for consistent cure times Work in a well-ventilated area to minimize fume exposure during long sets Store unopened bottles in the refrigerator (32°F–41°F / 0°C–5°C) to maximize shelf life After opening, store in a sealed thermo bag between sessions Storage and Safety Store in a cool, dark place (32°F–41°F / 0°C–5°C) away from direct sunlight and heat sources Keep bottle tightly sealed and away from moisture when not in use For professional external use only — intended for individual eyelash extension application Avoid contact with eyes; if contact occurs, rinse immediately with warm water and seek medical attention Keep out of reach of children Frequently Asked Questions What makes Cleopatra different from other Lovely US lash glues? Cleopatra stands out for its deep black pigment and smooth, balanced viscosity that minimizes clumping — making it the preferred choice for artists who prioritize a rich, defined lash line and precise placement. It also uses a horizontal shake technique rather than vertical, which helps maintain consistent texture. What is the difference between Cleopatra and Royal lash glue? Both have a 1-second dry time, but Cleopatra is distinguished by its deeper black pigment and anti-clump viscosity, while Royal is the best-selling worldwide formula known for high flexibility and broad technique versatility. What is the difference between Cleopatra and Ideal lash glue? Both offer 1-second dry time and work across classic and volume techniques. Ideal has higher flexibility and minimal fumes as its key differentiators, while Cleopatra’s defining features are its deep black pigment and smooth, clump-resistant texture. What are the ingredients in Cleopatra lash glue? Ethyl Cyanoacrylate, Methoxyethyl Cyanoacrylate, Polymethyl Methacrylate, CI 77266. How long does Cleopatra lash glue last on lashes? Cleopatra provides up to 8 weeks of retention under proper conditions when applied correctly and maintained with appropriate lash aftercare. Is Cleopatra lash glue good for volume lashes? Yes. Cleopatra’s smooth, balanced viscosity and 1-second dry time make it well-suited for volume and mega volume fan work, providing precise control without clumping. Where is Cleopatra lash glue made? Cleopatra Eyelash Extension Glue is manufactured in South Korea. About Lovely US Lovely US is one of the largest professional lash supply brands in the world, serving over 5,000 lash artists across North America and tens of thousands globally. Every adhesive formula is developed and refined over 8+ years to meet the performance demands of working professionals. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed on every order.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9355512807701</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extension Adhesive</param>
        <param name="Expiration Date" noFilter="true">10/21/2026</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9480101921045" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/rili-cookie-lash-extensions-16-lines-mix</url>
        <price>12</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Glue_In_Order_4700_x_4700_px.png?v=1771960569</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/jeXeyqrGQxh56T15fZfo_4821_webp.webp?v=1771957836</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/9l0v0e048ri7ash7jkietfxtgagsb5rc_d46dda8e-6d78-4ec2-af97-b08279a83256.jpg?v=1771957836</picture>
        <name>Rili Cookie Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | Brown | C D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 6–15mm |</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>COOKIE-C-007-6-13MM</vendorCode>
        <description>RILI COOKIE — Milk Chocolate Lash Extensions for Effortless Natural Beauty Discover the perfect soft brown shade with Rili Cookie eyelash extensions . This delicate milk chocolate color is the essential addition to the Rili brown lash collection, designed specifically for creating the most natural-looking lash enhancements. The warm, gentle brown tone creates a soft, approachable aesthetic that enhances beauty without overwhelming it. Why Lash Artists Choose Rili Cookie Rili Cookie is the go-to choice for professional lash technicians seeking versatility in natural lash work. The soft milk chocolate shade provides a warm, natural look that&apos;s perfect for clients with light hair colors, while adding lightness and airiness to brunettes&apos; overall appearance. This shade bridges the gap between bold definition and subtle enhancement. Premium Quality Features High-Quality Korean Fiber: Extensively tested by Glory Group technologists to ensure consistent quality and performance Optimal Tape Adhesion: Perfect density for both hand-made fans and strip lashing techniques Superior Consistency: Precise length, curl, and thickness specifications across all lashes Foil Backing: Professional-grade backing for easy handling and application 16 Lines Per Tray: Ample supply for multiple client applications Available in Three Stylish Shades Complete your lash collection with Black , Choco , Cookie , and Toffee to offer clients versatile color options for every look and preference. Professional Application Remove the desired number of lashes from the strip using precision tweezers. Create single lash applications or form custom volume fans according to your preferred technique. Use with professional-grade lash extension adhesive following manufacturer instructions. Product Specifications Color: Milk chocolate brown Lines: 16 lines per tray Backing: Foil Curl: Multiple options available Thickness: Multiple options available Length: Multiple options available Material: Premium Korean fiber Use: For external professional use only Storage &amp; Safety Store at room temperature away from direct sunlight and heating sources. Keep out of reach of children. For professional use only. Elevate your lash artistry with Rili Cookie — the must-have shade for natural, effortless beauty.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9480101921045</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">brown lashes, natural lash extensions, professional lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">6-13mm, 8-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">COOKIE-C-007-6-13MM, COOKIE-C-007-8-15MM, COOKIE-C-010-6-13MM, COOKIE-C-010-8-15MM, COOKIE-D-007-6-13MM, COOKIE-D-007-8-15MM, COOKIE-D-010-6-13MM, COOKIE-D-010-8-15MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">8</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9480099135765" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/rili-choco-lash-extensions-16-lines-mix</url>
        <price>12</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/al41u68bspmcvfcfbsvplf6dizt1ot91.jpg?v=1771627722</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/pz1tllvz1bzyu3rt3r8u0o2tm352pv4x.jpg?v=1771627722</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/9l0v0e048ri7ash7jkietfxtgagsb5rc_d46dda8e-6d78-4ec2-af97-b08279a83256.jpg?v=1771957836</picture>
        <name>Rili Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | MIX | Choco | C/D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 6–15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>CHOCO-C-007-6-13MM</vendorCode>
        <description>RILI CHOCO — Rich Brown Lash Extensions for Natural Depth Discover the perfect balance of warmth and definition with Rili Choco eyelash extensions . This rich chocolate brown shade creates a naturally enhanced look with subtle depth and dimension. Ideal for clients seeking a softer alternative to black while maintaining noticeable definition, Rili Choco delivers sophisticated elegance that complements any eye color. Why Lash Artists Choose Rili Choco Rili Choco is the go-to choice for professional lash technicians who want to create natural-looking volume with more depth than lighter brown shades. The rich chocolate tone adds beautiful dimension without the stark intensity of traditional black extensions, perfect for clients with warm undertones or those seeking a softer lash look. Premium Quality Features High-Quality Korean Fiber: Hypoallergenic synthetic monofilament polybutylene terephthalate ensures client safety and comfort 95% Quality Consistency: No curved tips, with precise length, curl, and thickness specifications Superior Tape Density: Rated 4 out of 5 by industry experts — significantly higher than Chinese alternatives Reusable Foil Backing: Innovative design allows tape to be reapplied to the pad multiple times for maximum efficiency 16 Lines Per Tray: Ample supply for multiple client applications Available in Three Stylish Shades Complete your lash collection with Black , Choco , and Toffee to offer clients versatile color options for every look. Professional Application Remove the desired number of lashes from the strip using precision tweezers. Create single lash applications or form custom volume fans according to your preferred technique. Use with professional-grade lash extension adhesive following manufacturer instructions. Product Specifications Lines: 16 lines per tray Material: Synthetic monofilament polybutylene terephthalate Origin: Made in Vietnam Use: For external professional use only Storage &amp; Safety Store at room temperature away from direct sunlight and heating sources. Keep out of reach of children. For professional use only. Elevate your lash artistry with Rili Choco — where premium quality meets natural elegance.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9480099135765</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">brown lashes, natural lash extensions, professional lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">6-13mm, 8-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">CHOCO-C-007-6-13MM, CHOCO-C-007-8-15MM, CHOCO-C-010-6-13MM, CHOCO-C-010-8-15MM, CHOCO-D-007-6-13MM, CHOCO-D-007-8-15MM, CHOCO-D-010-6-13MM, CHOCO-D-010-8-15MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">8</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9480097005845" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/rili-toffee-lash-extensions-16-lines</url>
        <price>12</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/2sysv7lrj4j2fr56a7me88bonjx2nuqv.jpg?v=1771625582</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/9l0v0e048ri7ash7jkietfxtgagsb5rc.jpg?v=1771625582</picture>
        <name>Rili Toffee Brown Eyelash Extensions | 16-Line Tray | C/D Curl | 0.07–0.10mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TOFFEE-C-007-6-13MM</vendorCode>
        <description>RILI TOFFEE — Warm Caramel Lash Extensions for Natural Beauty Discover the perfect balance of warmth and subtlety with Rili Toffee eyelash extensions . This soft light brown shade features a beautiful warm caramel undertone that creates the look of naturally well-groomed lashes. Ideal for clients seeking a gentle, harmonious enhancement without excessive boldness, Rili Toffee delivers a sophisticated warmth that complements any eye color. Why Lash Artists Choose Rili Toffee Rili Toffee is the go-to choice for professional lash technicians who want to enhance natural beauty while maintaining a soft, approachable aesthetic. The delicate caramel tone adds dimension and depth without the stark contrast of traditional black extensions. Premium Quality Features High-Quality Korean Fiber: Hypoallergenic synthetic monofilament polybutylene terephthalate ensures client safety and comfort 95% Quality Consistency: No curved tips, with precise length, curl, and thickness specifications Superior Tape Density: Rated 4 out of 5 by industry experts — significantly higher than Chinese alternatives Reusable Foil Backing: Innovative design allows tape to be reapplied to the pad multiple times for maximum efficiency 16 Lines Per Tray: Ample supply for multiple client applications Available in Three Stylish Shades Complete your lash collection with Black , Choco , and Toffee to offer clients versatile color options for every look. Professional Application Remove the desired number of lashes from the strip using precision tweezers. Create single lash applications or form custom volume fans according to your preferred technique. Use with professional-grade lash extension adhesive following manufacturer instructions. Product Specifications Lines: 16 lines per tray Material: Synthetic monofilament polybutylene terephthalate Origin: Made in Vietnam Use: For external professional use only Storage &amp; Safety Store at room temperature away from direct sunlight and heating sources. Keep out of reach of children. For professional use only. Elevate your lash artistry with Rili Toffee — where premium quality meets natural elegance.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9480097005845</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">brown lashes, Korean fiber lashes, natural lash extensions, professional lashes, toffee lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">6-13mm, 8-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TOFFEE-C-007-6-13MM, TOFFEE-C-007-8-15MM, TOFFEE-C-010-6-13MM, TOFFEE-C-010-8-15MM, TOFFEE-D-007-6-13MM, TOFFEE-D-007-8-15MM, TOFFEE-D-010-6-13MM, TOFFEE-D-010-8-15MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">8</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427395019029" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-45-eyelash-extension-tweezers-with-band-1</url>
        <price>21.25</price>
        <oldprice>25</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/lashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_45degreeswithband_5mm1.jpg?v=1760972942</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_45degreeswithband_5mm2.jpg?v=1760972942</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_45degreeswithband_5mm3.jpg?v=1760972942</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_45degreeswithband_5mm4.jpg?v=1760972942</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series 45° Eyelash Extension Tweezers (With Band)</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>LUS-TWZ-DIAM-45-BAND</vendorCode>
        <description>Diamond Series 45° Eyelash Extension Tweezers (With Band) 5mm Made from high-quality stainless steel , the Diamond Series features a micro-textured finish on the tips — created through a high-pressure machining process that applies fine stainless-steel dust to the surface. This precision technique improves grip on lash fibers, prevents slipping, and ensures steady fan control. The 45° angled tip enables easy removal of lash bundles from the strip without damaging or separating the base. The band grip design ensures comfort, control, and reduced hand strain during extended use. Recommended for: • Picking up and placing lash extensions with precision • Working on inner corners or deep-set eyes • Forming fans by hand or directly from the strip A professional-grade tool engineered for consistent performance and accuracy.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427395019029</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">LUS-TWZ-DIAM-45-BAND</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427422216469" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-90-eyelash-extension-tweezers-7-mm-tip</url>
        <price>21.25</price>
        <oldprice>25</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_7mm1_6478fe45-8427-4b59-829b-6f2f3f393756.jpg?v=1760979559</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_7mm2_7535f3f5-9b15-4497-be4a-00ffd98dd26a.jpg?v=1760979559</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_7mm3_7d88ec42-53d9-4f4e-9b14-9b16b5f61d36.jpg?v=1760979559</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_7mm4_0c2324d6-4615-492f-bef9-24985d4b30ea.jpg?v=1760979559</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series 90° Eyelash Extension Tweezers – 7 mm Tip</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-DS-90-7MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Diamond Series 90° Eyelash Extension Tweezers – 7 mm Tip Made from high-quality stainless steel , the Diamond Series features a micro-textured finish on the tips — created through a high-pressure machining process that applies fine stainless-steel dust to the surface. This precision technique improves grip on lash fibers, prevents slipping, and ensures steady fan control. The 90° angled tip (7 mm) allows you to lift and remove lash bundles from the strip without splitting or damaging the fan base . The extended 7 mm tip offers a wider working surface, providing greater flexibility and visibility during application. Recommended for: • Picking up and placing artificial lashes on natural lashes • Forming lash bundles both from the ribbon and by hand • Working in the inner corner of the eye • Ideal for small, short, or tufted lashes that require precise control A professional tool designed for comfort, stability, and consistent accuracy during every lash application.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427422216469</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-DS-90-7MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427417465109" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-standard-curved-eyelash-extension-tweezers</url>
        <price>25</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardCurvedEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries1.jpg?v=1760978586</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardCurvedEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries2.jpg?v=1760978586</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardCurvedEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries3.jpg?v=1760978586</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardCurvedEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries4.jpg?v=1760978586</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series Standard Curved Eyelash Extension Tweezers</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-DIAM-CURV-STD</vendorCode>
        <description>Diamond Series Standard Curved Eyelash Extension Tweezers Made from high-quality stainless steel , the Diamond Series features a micro-textured finish on the tips — created through a high-pressure machining process that applies fine stainless-steel dust to the surface. This precision technique improves grip on lash fibers, prevents slipping, and ensures steady fan control. The Standard Curved tweezer features moderately sharp, even-length tips designed for pinpoint isolation of a single eyelash . The gentle curvature allows for a more comfortable angle during isolation and placement, making it ideal for extended work sessions. Recommended for: • Precise isolation and separation of natural lashes • Safe and convenient extraction of individual lashes • Controlled handling during classic and volume lash applications A professional-grade tool engineered for precision, comfort, and balance in every lash application.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427417465109</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-DIAM-CURV-STD</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427420446997" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-45-eyelash-extension-tweezers-7-mm-tip</url>
        <price>21.25</price>
        <oldprice>25</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_7mm1.jpg?v=1760979215</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_7mm2.jpg?v=1760979215</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_7mm3.jpg?v=1760979215</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Eyelash_ExtensionT_weezers_Lovely_Diamondseries_90degrees_7mm4.jpg?v=1771447763</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series 45° Eyelash Extension Tweezers – 7 mm Tip</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-DIA-45-7MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Diamond Series 45° Eyelash Extension Tweezers – 7 mm Tip Made from high-quality stainless steel , the Diamond Series features a micro-textured finish on the tips — created through a high-pressure machining process that applies fine stainless-steel dust to the surface. This precision technique improves grip on lash fibers, prevents slipping, and ensures steady fan control. The 45° angled tip (7 mm) allows you to easily grab and remove lash bundles from the tape without disintegrating the fan base . The precise external angle is designed for clean, effortless handling of lashes in any area of the eye. Recommended for: • Grabbing artificial lashes and placing them on natural lashes • Working on inner corners and deep-set eyes with comfort and precision • Forming lash bundles both from the ribbon and by hand • Providing consistent control when isolating or positioning lashes A professional-grade tool engineered for balance, accuracy, and steady performance throughout every lash application.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427420446997</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-DIA-45-7MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427419037973" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-boot-eyelash-extension-tweezers</url>
        <price>21.25</price>
        <oldprice>25</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_Boot.jpg?v=1760978915</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_Boot2.jpg?v=1760978915</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_Boot3.jpg?v=1760978915</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_Boot4.jpg?v=1760978915</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series Boot Eyelash Extension Tweezers</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-BOOT-DS</vendorCode>
        <description>Precision-Engineered for Professional Lash Artists The Diamond Series Boot Eyelash Extension Tweezers deliver the exceptional grip and control you need for flawless volume fan creation and precise lash placement. Crafted from premium stainless steel with a signature boot-shaped tip, these tweezers are designed to elevate your lash artistry. Why Lash Artists Choose Diamond Series Perfect Boot Tip Design – Ideal grip angle for creating uniform volume fans and picking up multiple extensions Feather-Light Tension – Reduces hand fatigue during long appointment sessions Premium Stainless Steel – Corrosion-resistant, autoclave-safe, and built to last Precision-Aligned Tips – Hand-tested for perfect closure with no gaps or misalignment Ergonomic Balance – Comfortable grip that gives you complete control over every placement Professional Performance You Can Trust Whether you&apos;re creating mega volume fans or isolating natural lashes, the Diamond Series Boot Tweezers provide the tactile feedback and reliability that professional lash technicians demand. The boot tip shape allows you to scoop and fan extensions effortlessly, making your workflow faster and more efficient. Specifications: Premium stainless steel construction | Boot-shaped tip | Lightweight design | Easy to clean and sterilize Upgrade your lash toolkit with tweezers that match your professional standards.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427419037973</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">boot tip tweezers, diamond series, lash extension tools, professional tweezers, volume lash tweezers</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-BOOT-DS</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427418480917" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-round-boot-eyelash-extension-tweezers</url>
        <price>21.25</price>
        <oldprice>25</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_RoundBoot1.jpg?v=1760978738</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_RoundBoot2.jpg?v=1760978738</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_RoundBoot3.jpg?v=1760978738</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_RoundBoot4.jpg?v=1760978738</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series Round Boot Eyelash Extension Tweezers</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>LUS-TWZ-BOOT-RD</vendorCode>
        <description>Precision-Engineered for Professional Lash Artists The Diamond Series Round Boot Eyelash Extension Tweezers combine the versatility of a rounded tip with the fan-making power of a boot design. Perfect for lash artists who want exceptional control for both volume work and precise isolation. Why Lash Artists Choose Diamond Series Unique Round Boot Tip – Rounded edges provide gentle lash pickup while maintaining boot functionality for volume fans Versatile Performance – Seamlessly switch between isolation, pickup, and fan creation with one tool Premium Stainless Steel – Corrosion-resistant, autoclave-safe, and built for daily professional use Precision-Aligned Tips – Hand-tested for perfect closure with no gaps or misalignment Feather-Light Tension – Reduces hand fatigue during extended lash sessions Ergonomic Balance – Comfortable grip that gives you complete control over every placement Professional Performance You Can Trust Whether you&apos;re creating classic sets or mega volume fans, the Diamond Series Round Boot Tweezers adapt to your technique. The rounded boot tip allows for gentle lash handling while maintaining the scooping action needed for efficient fan creation, making your workflow smoother and more versatile. Specifications: Premium stainless steel construction | Round boot-shaped tip | Lightweight design | Easy to clean and sterilize Upgrade your lash toolkit with tweezers that match your professional standards.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427418480917</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">diamond series, lash extension tools, professional tweezers, round boot tweezers, volume lash tweezers</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">LUS-TWZ-BOOT-RD</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427406127381" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-standard-straight-eyelash-extension-tweezers-with-band</url>
        <price>21.25</price>
        <oldprice>25</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardStraightwithbandEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries1.jpg?v=1760976578</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardStraightwithbandEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries4.jpg?v=1760976579</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardStraightwithbandEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries2.jpg?v=1760976578</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardStraightwithbandEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries3.jpg?v=1760976578</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series Standard Straight Eyelash Extension Tweezers (With Band)</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-DIAM-STR-BAND</vendorCode>
        <description>Diamond Series Standard Straight Eyelash Extension Tweezers (With Band) Made from high-quality stainless steel , the Diamond Series features a micro-textured finish on the tips — created through a high-pressure machining process that applies fine stainless-steel dust to the surface. This precision technique improves grip on lash fibers, prevents slipping, and ensures steady fan control. The Standard Straight tweezer has moderately sharp, even-length tips , allowing for accurate isolation and the ability to pinpoint a single natural lash. The band grip provides improved comfort and stability for long lash sessions. Recommended for: • Isolating and separating individual natural lashes • Precise extraction of natural eyelashes during application • Tasks that require straight, steady alignment and clean visibility A dependable tool for lash artists who value precision, balance, and comfort in every movement.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427406127381</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-DIAM-STR-BAND</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427413238037" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-standard-straight-eyelash-extension-tweezers</url>
        <price>21.25</price>
        <oldprice>25</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardStraightEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries1.jpg?v=1760977879</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardStraightEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries2.jpg?v=1760977879</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardStraightEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries3.jpg?v=1760977879</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/StandardStraightEyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries4.jpg?v=1760977879</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series Standard Straight Eyelash Extension Tweezers</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-DS-STR</vendorCode>
        <description>Diamond Series Standard Straight Eyelash Extension Tweezers Made from high-quality stainless steel , the Diamond Series features a micro-textured finish on the tips — created through a high-pressure machining process that applies fine stainless-steel dust to the surface. This precision technique improves grip on lash fibers, prevents slipping, and ensures steady fan control. The Standard Straight tweezer has moderately sharp, even-length tips , allowing for accurate isolation and the ability to pinpoint a single natural lash. The band grip provides improved comfort and stability for long lash sessions. Recommended for: • Isolating and separating individual natural lashes • Precise extraction of natural eyelashes during application • Tasks that require straight, steady alignment and clean visibility A dependable tool for lash artists who value precision, balance, and comfort in every movement.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427413238037</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-DS-STR</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427421069589" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-45-eyelash-extension-tweezers-5-mm-tip</url>
        <price>25</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_45degrees_5mm1.jpg?v=1760979334</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_45degrees_5mm2.jpg?v=1760979334</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_45degrees_5mm3.jpg?v=1760979334</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_45degrees_5mm4.jpg?v=1760979334</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series 45° Eyelash Extension Tweezers – 5 mm Tip</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-DS-45-5MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Diamond Series 45° Eyelash Extension Tweezers – 5 mm Tip Made from high-quality stainless steel , the Diamond Series features a micro-textured finish on the tips — created through a high-pressure machining process that applies fine stainless-steel dust to the surface. This precision technique improves grip on lash fibers, prevents slipping, and ensures steady fan control. The 45° angled tip (5 mm) provides precise access for detailed lash work. Its smaller tip size allows the artist to grab and remove lash bundles from the tape without damaging or separating the fan base , ensuring clean and consistent results. Recommended for: • Picking up and placing artificial lashes on natural lashes • Working with inner corners and deep-set eyes where precision is needed • Forming lash fans both from the strip and by hand A professional tool designed for exceptional balance, comfort, and accuracy in every lash application.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427421069589</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-DS-45-5MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9427421593877" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/diamond-series-90-eyelash-extension-tweezers-5-mm-tip</url>
        <price>21.25</price>
        <oldprice>25</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_5mm1_6c68e6ca-f4c9-40c1-a80e-8b1dc00b0f56.jpg?v=1760979465</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_5mm2.jpg?v=1760979465</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_5mm3.jpg?v=1760979464</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/EyelashExtensionTweezersLovelyDiamondseries_90degrees_5mm4.jpg?v=1760979464</picture>
        <name>Diamond Series 90° Eyelash Extension Tweezers – 5 mm Tip</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>LVL-TWZ-DS90-5MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Diamond Series 90° Eyelash Extension Tweezers – 5 mm Tip Made from high-quality stainless steel , the Diamond Series features a micro-textured finish on the tips — created through a high-pressure machining process that applies fine stainless-steel dust to the surface. This precision technique improves grip on lash fibers, prevents slipping, and ensures steady fan control. The 90° angled tip (5 mm) allows you to lift and remove lash bundles from the strip without splitting or damaging the fan base . The precise angle ensures effortless handling and accurate placement, even in detailed areas. Recommended for: • Picking up and placing artificial lashes on natural lashes • Forming lash bundles both from the ribbon and by hand • Working in the inner corner of the eye • Perfect for small or tufted lashes that require extra precision A professional-grade tool engineered for balance, comfort, and exceptional accuracy in every lash application.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9427421593877</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">LVL-TWZ-DS90-5MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="3925471821891" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/adhesive-ring-double</url>
        <price>0.50</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>7</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/fa0038056055b33259ef6bbc85a5f103.jpg?v=1762457141</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/0U9A2644.jpg?v=1636037104</picture>
        <name>Adhesive rings - Double</name>
        <typePrefix>Related Materials</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ADHSV-RING</vendorCode>
        <description>Speed up your lash extension application with the Adhesive Ring Double — designed for precision and efficiency at every appointment. Single adhesive ring per unit Double-well design for multi-glue use Fits standard lash ring holders Hygienic single-use per client A must-have consumable for professional lash technicians and salons.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">3925471821891</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Related Materials</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">adhesive double ring, adhesive ring, double ring, ring</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ADHSV-RING</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="2106389397571" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/removable-tip-for-glue</url>
        <price>0.25</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>7</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/image_e715e0c2-fb02-4764-b291-b5e9e93a26c9.jpg?v=1762457135</picture>
        <name>Removable Tip For Glue</name>
        <typePrefix>Related Materials</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TIP-GLUE</vendorCode>
        <description>Removable Tips for Lash Extension Adhesive Upgrade your lash application workflow with these professional removable adhesive tips. Designed for precision and efficiency, they minimize waste and keep your glue nozzle clean between clients — essential for any busy lash technician or salon. Why Lash Pros Love It: Fits standard lash extension adhesive bottles Reduces clogging for a cleaner, more consistent glue flow Disposable &amp; hygienic — swap between clients with ease Lightweight and easy to handle during application Lovely US — Trusted by Professionals For over 8 years, we&apos;ve supplied 5,000+ lash professionals across North America with premium tools at accessible prices. Our mission: help you Enhance Beauty where you are.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">2106389397571</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Related Materials</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TIP-GLUE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1682953601091" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/nylon-brush</url>
        <price>0.15</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>7</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_22c06b5a-dc13-4328-b3e8-6d7ece6d50b9.jpg?v=1762457130</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_fe5c4364-d69d-45b8-82e8-b92f3749b84d.jpg?v=1682614396</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_5ec5a9b0-c599-4278-be1d-eebc601f1489.jpg?v=1682614396</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_13e2481b-6a90-4d13-9e09-68cd50ec38d2.jpg?v=1682614396</picture>
        <name>Nylon Brush</name>
        <typePrefix>Related Materials</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>NYLON-BRUSH</vendorCode>
        <description>Nylon Brushes for eyelashes 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed For over 8 years we have been bringing you the most professional products at affordable prices Brand One of the largest beauty brands worldwide we have over 5,000+ customers in North America and tens of thousands around the world. Our mission is to help you Enhance Beauty where you are. Shipping Orders are processed and shipped SAME DAY on all orders placed before 1pm Eastern Time Mon-Fri. Free Shipping in US on Orders over $100.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1682953601091</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Related Materials</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Nylon brushes, nylon eyelash brush, nylon eyelash brushes</param>
        <param name="Color" noFilter="true">Gold White</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">NYLON-BRUSH</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="2106387726403" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/temporary-bung-with-needle-for-glue</url>
        <price>0.25</price>
        <oldprice>0.50</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>7</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/image_4fa622bb-4963-4b78-9e29-91e4ce1859db.jpg?v=1762457133</picture>
        <name>Temporary Bung With Needle For Glue</name>
        <typePrefix>Related Materials</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>NEEDLE-GLUE</vendorCode>
        <description>Stop Glue Clogs Mid-Session This temporary needle bung fits directly into your lash adhesive bottle nozzle — preventing clogging and doubling as a cap while you work. No more stopping to twist and untwist the lid. Why Lash Techs Love It: Prevents nozzle clogging between uses Acts as a cap during the lash extension procedure Saves time — keep your flow without interruption Compatible with standard lash glue bottles Trusted by Professionals Lovely US has served 5,000+ customers across North America for over 8 years — delivering professional-grade tools at accessible prices.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">2106387726403</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Related Materials</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">NEEDLE-GLUE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4440240685107" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/royal-eyelash-extension-glue</url>
        <price>35</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>2</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Royal_Glue_-9916_4e398bf4-0675-4d95-9bd9-4a5c00ae5ec7.jpg?v=1776786577</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Royal_Glue_-9917_b73229f3-0f02-4828-9a89-6bc333bae18f.jpg?v=1776303899</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Royal_Glue.png?v=1779824746</picture>
        <name>Royal Eyelash Extension Glue – 1-Second Dry, 8-Week Hold, 5 ml</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extension Adhesive</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ROYAL-GLUE</vendorCode>
        <description>Royal Eyelash Extension Glue by Lovely US – 5 ml What is Royal Lash Glue? Royal Eyelash Extension Glue is a professional-grade, black lash adhesive manufactured by Lovely US. It features a 1-second drying time , 8-week retention , medium viscosity , and a formaldehyde-free formula . It is compatible with classic, volume, and mega volume eyelash extension techniques. Royal is the best-selling professional lash adhesive worldwide , trusted by over 5,000 lash artists across North America and tens of thousands globally. The formula has been continuously refined over 8+ years of professional use. Key Specifications Brand: Lovely US Volume: 5 ml Color: Black Drying time: 1 second Retention: Up to 8 weeks Viscosity: Medium Formula: Formaldehyde-free Compatible techniques: Classic, volume, mega volume Skill level: Experienced / professional lash technicians Country of origin: South Korea Why Lash Artists Choose Royal 1-second dry time — Industry-standard speed for experienced lash technicians who need reliable, fast curing 8-week retention — Long-lasting bond that reduces client touch-up frequency High flexibility — The cured adhesive moves naturally with lashes, improving all-day comfort for clients Medium viscosity — Provides precise control during application, ideal for detailed volume fan work Formaldehyde-free — Reduces irritation risk for both technician and client Proven formula — Refined over 8+ years based on real-world professional feedback Optimal Working Conditions For best results, use Royal Lash Glue in the following environment: Temperature: 66°F–77°F (18°C–23°C) Humidity: 40%–70% relative humidity Shelf life (unopened): 6 months from production date Shelf life (after opening): Use within 2 months for optimal performance How to Apply Royal Lash Glue Shake the bottle well before every use to ensure consistent viscosity Dispense a small drop onto a glue palette or jade stone Dip only the base of the lash extension into the adhesive Apply to the natural lash and hold briefly for a secure bond Replace the glue drop every 10 minutes to maintain freshness and optimal curing speed Professional Tips for Best Results Use a calibrated hygrometer to monitor your lash room&apos;s humidity — this is the single biggest factor affecting dry time Work in a well-ventilated area to minimize fume exposure during long sets Store unopened bottles in the refrigerator to maximize shelf life After opening, store in a sealed thermo bag between sessions to slow degradation Storage and Safety Store in a cool, dark place away from direct sunlight and heat sources Keep bottle tightly sealed when not in use For professional external use only — intended for individual eyelash extension application Avoid contact with eyes; if contact occurs, rinse immediately with warm water and seek medical attention Keep out of reach of children Frequently Asked Questions Is Royal Lash Glue good for beginners? Royal is designed for experienced lash technicians. Its 1-second dry time requires confident, practiced application. Beginners may prefer a slower-drying adhesive while building speed. What techniques is Royal compatible with? Royal works with classic, volume, and mega volume eyelash extension techniques. Is Royal Lash Glue formaldehyde-free? Yes. Royal Eyelash Extension Glue is formaldehyde-free, making it one of the safer professional adhesive options available. How long does Royal Lash Glue last on lashes? Royal provides up to 8 weeks of retention under normal conditions when applied correctly and maintained with proper aftercare. Where is Royal Lash Glue made? Royal Eyelash Extension Glue is manufactured in South Korea. About Lovely US Lovely US is one of the largest professional lash supply brands in the world, serving over 5,000 lash artists across North America and tens of thousands globally. Every adhesive formula is developed and refined over 8+ years to meet the demands of working professionals. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed on every order.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4440240685107</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extension Adhesive</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">1 second dry time, black adhesive, eyelash adhesive, eyelash extension adhesive, Eyelash extension glue, eyelash extensions glue, eyelash glue, formaldehyde-free, formaldehyde-free lash glue, lash adhesive, lash glue, professional lash glue, professional lash supplies, volume lash adhesive, volume lash glue</param>
        <param name="Expiration Date" noFilter="true">10/21/2026</param>
        <param name="Drying speed" noFilter="true">1 Second</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ROYAL-GLUE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1647125987395" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/eyelash-sealer-gentle</url>
        <price>15</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>6</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/untitled-9550.jpg?v=1762457129</picture>
        <name>Eyelash Extension Sealer - Gentle</name>
        <typePrefix>Preparations</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>EYE-SEALER-GENTLE</vendorCode>
        <description>Professional Eyelash Extension Sealer - Gentle Formula Extend retention and protect your clients&apos; lash extensions with our gentle sealer. This professional-grade formula creates an invisible protective barrier that shields extensions from environmental factors while nourishing natural lashes. Key Benefits Extended Retention: Increases adhesion duration between natural and extension lashes Nourishing Formula: Strengthens and conditions natural lashes without weighing them down Non-Sticky Application: Gentle sealer won&apos;t clump or stick lashes together Versatile Use: Compatible with both classic and volume lash applications Gentle Formula: Designed for comfortable, safe use Application Instructions Apply sealer directly to the bond area where natural and extension lashes meet. For optimal results, use immediately after lash application and recommend to clients for at-home maintenance 2-3 times per week. Product Specifications Shelf Life: 2 years unopened | 6 months after opening Origin: Made in Korea Volume: Professional size for salon use Safety Information For external use only. Avoid direct contact with eyes. If contact occurs, rinse thoroughly with water and consult a physician if irritation persists. Why LOVELY U.S. Our formulas are developed and refined through years of professional use, delivering consistent, reliable results for lash artists worldwide. We&apos;re committed to providing premium-quality products that enhance your technical work and keep clients coming back. Professional-grade quality. Trusted by lash artists globally.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1647125987395</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Preparations</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelash extension sealer, eyelash sealer, lash coating, sealer</param>
        <param name="Expiration date" noFilter="true">02/20/2028</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">EYE-SEALER-GENTLE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="2147288645699" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/black-lash-coating-tinting-effect</url>
        <price>10</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>6</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/untitled-1030.jpg?v=1762457135</picture>
        <name>Eyelash Extension Sealer - Tinting Effect</name>
        <typePrefix>Preparations</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>EYE-SEALER-BLACK-8/13/2027</vendorCode>
        <description>Professional Eyelash Extension Sealer - Tinting Effect Enhance retention and create a fuller, more dramatic lash appearance with our tinting effect sealer. This professional-grade formula nourishes and seals natural lashes to extensions while providing a subtle darkening effect for seamless, polished results. Key Benefits Tinting Effect: Darkens regrown light lashes for consistent color throughout wear Enhanced Color &amp; Luster: Intensifies lash color and adds natural shine Protective Barrier: Seals the bond point between natural and extension lashes Seamless Regrowth: Minimizes the appearance of lighter regrowth for a more uniform look Fuller Appearance: Creates a more dramatic, complete lash line Application Instructions Apply coating directly to the lashes immediately after the extension procedure. For optimal results, recommend to clients for at-home maintenance 2-3 times per week to maintain color intensity and protection. Product Specifications Shelf Life: 2 years unopened | 6 months after opening Effect: Tinting/darkening formula Volume: Professional size for salon use Safety Information For external use only. Avoid direct contact with eyes. If contact occurs, rinse thoroughly with water and consult a physician if irritation persists. Why LOVELY U.S. Our formulas are developed and refined through years of professional use, delivering consistent, reliable results for lash artists worldwide. We&apos;re committed to providing premium-quality products that enhance your technical work and keep clients coming back. Professional-grade quality. Trusted by lash artists globally.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">2147288645699</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Preparations</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelash coating, eyelash extension coating, eyelash extension sealer, eyelash sealer, lash coating, lash sealer, sealer</param>
        <param name="Expiration date" noFilter="true">8/13/2027, 1/20/2028</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">EYE-SEALER-BLACK-8/13/2027, EYE-SEALER-BLACK-1/20/2028</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">2</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4381304258611" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/clear-eyelash-extension-glue</url>
        <price>24</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>2</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Clear_Glue_-9933.jpg?v=1762457159</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Clear_Glue_-9935.jpg?v=1580848679</picture>
        <name>Clear Eyelash Extension Glue – Invisible Bond, 1-Second Dry, 5 ml</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extension Adhesive</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>CLEAR-GLUE</vendorCode>
        <description>Clear Eyelash Extension Glue by Lovely US – 5 ml What is Clear Lash Glue? Clear Eyelash Extension Glue is a professional-grade, transparent lash adhesive manufactured by Lovely US. It features a 1-second drying time , 8-week retention , medium viscosity , and medium-to-high flexibility . Unlike black adhesives, it dries completely clear, creating an invisible bond that does not show through lighter or colored lash extensions. Clear is the go-to adhesive for lash artists offering brown lashes, blonde lashes, colored lash extensions , or any application where a seamless, natural-looking lash line is the goal. It is suitable for all skill levels, from beginners to expert lash technicians. Key Specifications Brand: Lovely US Volume: 5 ml Color when cured: Clear / transparent (invisible) Drying time: 1 second Retention: Up to 8 weeks Viscosity: Medium Flexibility: Medium to high Compatible techniques: Classic and volume eyelash extensions Skill level: All levels — beginner through expert Best for: Brown, blonde, and colored lash extensions Country of origin: South Korea Why Lash Artists Choose Clear Invisible bond — Dries completely clear with no visible adhesive line, essential for brown and colored lash applications 1-second dry time — Fast, reliable curing for efficient application across all skill levels 8-week retention — Long-lasting hold that keeps clients satisfied between fills Medium viscosity — Smooth, controlled consistency for precise placement on fine or colored extensions Medium-to-high flexibility — Comfortable bond that moves naturally with lashes throughout the day All skill levels — Accessible for beginners while still delivering professional results for experts Versatile — Works with classic and volume techniques across a wide range of lash colors When to Use Clear Lash Glue Clear adhesive is the correct choice when a black adhesive would be visible or detract from the finished look: Brown lash extensions — prevents a dark adhesive line from showing at the lash base Blonde lash extensions — maintains a seamless, natural appearance on light-colored lashes Colored lash extensions (blue, purple, red, green, etc.) — keeps the bond invisible so the color pops Clients with light natural lashes — avoids a harsh contrast at the lash line Natural or no-makeup looks — ideal for clients who want subtle lash enhancement Creative and editorial lash designs — where adhesive visibility would compromise the aesthetic Optimal Working Conditions For consistent 1-second curing, maintain the following environment: Temperature: 66°F–77°F (18°C–23°C) Humidity: 40%–70% relative humidity Shelf life (unopened): 6 months from production date Shelf life (after opening): Use within 2 months for optimal performance How to Apply Clear Lash Glue Shake the bottle well before every use to ensure consistent viscosity Dispense a small drop onto a glue palette or jade stone Dip only the base of the lash extension into the adhesive Apply to the natural lash for a secure, invisible bond Replace the glue drop every 10 minutes to maintain freshness and curing speed Professional Tips for Best Results Clear adhesive is essential for any lash menu that includes brown or colored lash services Use a calibrated hygrometer to monitor room humidity for consistent cure times Work in a well-ventilated area to minimize fume exposure during long sets Store unopened bottles in the refrigerator to extend shelf life After opening, store in a sealed thermo bag between sessions Storage and Safety Store in a cool, dark place away from direct sunlight and heat sources Keep bottle tightly sealed when not in use For professional external use only — intended for individual eyelash extension application Avoid contact with eyes; if contact occurs, rinse immediately with warm water and seek medical attention Keep out of reach of children Frequently Asked Questions What is clear lash glue used for? Clear lash glue is used when a transparent, invisible bond is needed — most commonly for brown, blonde, and colored eyelash extensions where a black adhesive would show through and create an unwanted dark line at the lash base. Is clear lash glue as strong as black lash glue? Yes. Lovely US Clear Lash Glue provides the same 1-second dry time and up to 8 weeks of retention as comparable black adhesives. The clear formula does not compromise bond strength. Can beginners use clear lash glue? Yes. Unlike ultra-fast adhesives, Clear Lash Glue is suitable for all skill levels, including beginners, due to its 1-second dry time and medium viscosity. What is the difference between clear and black lash glue? The primary difference is color when cured. Black adhesive dries dark and is standard for black lash extensions. Clear adhesive dries transparent and is used for brown, blonde, or colored extensions where an invisible bond is required. How long does clear lash glue last on lashes? Lovely US Clear Lash Glue provides up to 8 weeks of retention under proper conditions when applied correctly and maintained with appropriate lash aftercare. Where is Lovely US Clear Lash Glue made? It is manufactured in South Korea. About Lovely US Lovely US is one of the largest professional lash supply brands in the world, serving over 5,000 lash artists across North America and tens of thousands globally. Every adhesive formula is developed and refined over 8+ years to meet the performance demands of working professionals. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed on every order.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4381304258611</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extension Adhesive</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">1 second dry time, brown lash glue, brown lashes, clear adhesive, clear lash adhesive, colored lash adhesive, colored lashes, eyelash adhesive, eyelash extension adhesive, Eyelash extension glue, eyelash extensions glue, eyelash glue, invisible lash bond, lash adhesive, lash glue, professional lash supplies</param>
        <param name="Expiration Date" noFilter="true">10/21/2026</param>
        <param name="Drying speed" noFilter="true">1 Second</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">CLEAR-GLUE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4381323755571" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/pure-eyelash-extension-glue-sensive-eyes</url>
        <price>24</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>2</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Pure_Glue_-9925_1e89082e-1a5d-4d24-af06-8b2b95fe05d4.jpg?v=1762457159</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Pure_Glue_-9926_abdd2d4d-72d3-4139-a174-76084dd20465.jpg?v=1602333487</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Pure_Platform.png?v=1779825754</picture>
        <name>Pure Eyelash Extension Glue For Sensitive Eyes – Hypoallergenic, 4-5 Second Dry, 5 ml</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extension Adhesive</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>PURE-GLUE-Hypoallergenic</vendorCode>
        <description>Pure Eyelash Extension Glue For Sensitive Eyes by Lovely US – 5 ml What is Pure Lash Glue? Pure Eyelash Extension Glue is a professional-grade, hypoallergenic lash adhesive manufactured by Lovely US, specifically formulated for clients with sensitive eyes. It features a 4–5 second drying time , 4-week retention , thin viscosity , medium flexibility , zero evaporation , and a no-fume formula that does not cause tearing or irritation. It is compatible with classic and light volume eyelash extension techniques and is suitable for all skill levels, including beginners. Pure is the gentlest professional lash adhesive in the Lovely US lineup — the go-to choice for lash artists who serve clients with sensitive eyes, allergies to standard adhesives, or a history of irritation during lash appointments. Key Specifications Brand: Lovely US Volume: 5 ml Color: Black Drying time: 4–5 seconds Retention: Up to 4 weeks Viscosity: Thin Flexibility: Medium Fume level: None / zero evaporation Formula: Hypoallergenic Compatible techniques: Classic and light volume eyelash extensions Skill level: All levels — beginner through expert Best for: Sensitive eyes, allergy-prone clients, beginners Country of origin: South Korea Why Lash Artists Choose Pure Hypoallergenic formula — Specially developed to minimize allergic reactions in clients with sensitive eyes or adhesive sensitivities Zero evaporation / no fumes — Does not cause tearing, redness, or irritation during application — the most comfortable lash experience possible 4–5 second dry time — Slower curing gives lash artists time to adjust placement, making it ideal for beginners and precision work 4-week retention — Reliable hold appropriate for sensitive-eye clients who may have shorter natural lash cycles Thin viscosity — Smooth, easy application with precise control for clean, natural-looking bonds Medium flexibility — Comfortable bond that moves naturally with lashes throughout the day Beginner-friendly — The forgiving dry time allows new lash artists to build confidence and refine technique When to Use Pure Lash Glue Pure is the correct adhesive choice in the following situations: Clients with sensitive eyes — reduces risk of irritation, redness, and tearing during and after application Clients with known adhesive allergies — hypoallergenic formula lowers the likelihood of allergic reactions Clients who experience tearing with standard adhesives — zero evaporation eliminates the fume-related tearing common with faster adhesives Beginner lash artists — the 4–5 second window allows time for repositioning and learning proper technique Classic and light volume sets — ideal for natural, subtle lash looks where comfort is the priority Clients transitioning from strip lashes — a gentle introduction to lash extension adhesives Optimal Working Conditions Temperature: 66°F–77°F (18°C–23°C) Humidity: 40%–70% relative humidity Shelf life (unopened): 6 months from production date Shelf life (after opening): Use within 2 months for optimal performance How to Apply Pure Lash Glue Shake the bottle well before every use to ensure consistent thin viscosity Dispense a small drop onto a glue palette or jade stone Dip only the base of the lash extension into the adhesive Apply to the natural lash — the 4–5 second window allows for gentle repositioning if needed Replace the glue drop every 10 minutes to maintain freshness and performance Professional Tips for Best Results Always perform a patch test 24–48 hours before a full lash set for clients with known sensitivities or allergy history Pure is an excellent adhesive for building a sensitive-client specialty service — a growing and underserved market segment The slower dry time makes Pure ideal for training new lash artists on proper isolation and placement technique Use a calibrated hygrometer to monitor room humidity for consistent curing Work in a well-ventilated area even with a no-fume formula — best practice for all lash services Store unopened bottles in the refrigerator to extend shelf life After opening, store in a sealed thermo bag between sessions Storage and Safety Store in a cool, dark place away from direct sunlight and heat sources Keep bottle tightly sealed when not in use For professional external use only — intended for individual eyelash extension application Avoid contact with eyes; if contact occurs, rinse immediately with warm water and seek medical attention Keep out of reach of children Frequently Asked Questions What is hypoallergenic lash glue? Hypoallergenic lash glue is formulated to minimize the risk of allergic reactions during eyelash extension application. Pure by Lovely US achieves this through a no-fume, zero-evaporation formula that eliminates the primary irritants found in standard professional adhesives. Is Pure lash glue safe for sensitive eyes? Yes. Pure is specifically formulated for clients with sensitive eyes. Its zero-evaporation, no-fume formula does not cause tearing or irritation, making it the safest adhesive option in the Lovely US lineup for sensitive clients. What is the difference between Pure and standard lash glues like Royal or Ideal? Pure has a much slower dry time (4–5 seconds vs. 1 second), lower retention (4 weeks vs. 8 weeks), and zero fumes — all trade-offs made to prioritize client comfort and safety for sensitive eyes. Royal and Ideal are designed for experienced artists working with non-sensitive clients who need faster curing and longer retention. Can beginners use Pure lash glue? Yes. Pure is one of the most beginner-friendly adhesives available. The 4–5 second dry time gives new lash artists a comfortable window to adjust placement and build proper technique without rushing. How long does Pure lash glue last on lashes? Pure provides up to 4 weeks of retention. This is shorter than standard adhesives due to the gentler formula, but appropriate for sensitive-eye clients who may also have more delicate natural lashes. Does Pure lash glue cause tearing? No. Pure’s zero-evaporation formula produces no fumes, which is the primary cause of tearing during lash extension application with standard adhesives. Where is Pure lash glue made? Pure Eyelash Extension Glue is manufactured in South Korea. About Lovely US Lovely US is one of the largest professional lash supply brands in the world, serving over 5,000 lash artists across North America and tens of thousands globally. Every adhesive formula is developed and refined over 8+ years to meet the performance demands of working professionals. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed on every order.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4381323755571</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extension Adhesive</param>
        <param name="Expiration Date" noFilter="true">10/21/2026</param>
        <param name="Drying speed" noFilter="true">4-5 Seconds</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">PURE-GLUE-Hypoallergenic</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4381356884019" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/elite-eyelash-extension-glue</url>
        <price>40</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>2</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Elite_Glue_-9920.jpg?v=1776303899</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Elite_Glue_-9919.jpg?v=1776303899</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Elite_Platform.png?v=1779825024</picture>
        <name>Elite Eyelash Extension Glue – 0.5-Second Dry, 8-Week Hold, 5 ml</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extension Adhesive</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ELITE-GLUE</vendorCode>
        <description>Elite Eyelash Extension Glue by Lovely US – 5 ml What is Elite Lash Glue? Elite Eyelash Extension Glue is an ultra-fast, professional-grade black lash adhesive manufactured by Lovely US. It features a 0.5-second (instant) drying time , 8-week retention , thin viscosity , medium flexibility , and a low-fume formula . It is designed exclusively for expert-level lash technicians and is compatible with both classic and volume eyelash extension techniques. Elite is the fastest-drying professional lash adhesive in the Lovely US lineup, trusted by experienced lash masters who need maximum speed and bond strength without sacrificing client comfort. Key Specifications Brand: Lovely Volume: 5 ml Color: Black Drying time: 0.5 seconds (instant) Retention: Up to 8 weeks Viscosity: Thin Flexibility: Medium Fume level: Low / minimal Compatible techniques: Classic and volume eyelash extensions Skill level: Expert / advanced lash technicians only Country of origin: South Korea Why Lash Artists Choose Elite 0.5-second instant dry time — The fastest adhesive in the Lovely US range, built for expert hands that move with precision and speed 8-week retention — Long-lasting bond that reduces client fill frequency and increases satisfaction Strongest bond available — Maximum adhesive strength for secure, durable results across all lash types Thin viscosity — Smooth, fluid consistency for fast pick-up and precise placement on fine natural lashes Medium flexibility — Strong bond that still moves naturally with lashes for all-day client comfort Low fume formula — Minimizes vapor exposure for both technician and client during long sets Proven formula — Refined over 8+ years of professional development and real-world feedback Optimal Working Conditions For consistent 0.5-second curing, maintain the following environment: Temperature: 66°F–77°F (18°C–23°C) Humidity: 40%–70% relative humidity Shelf life (unopened): 6 months from production date Shelf life (after opening): Use within 2 months for optimal performance How to Apply Elite Lash Glue Shake the bottle well before every use to ensure consistent thin viscosity Dispense a small drop onto a glue palette or jade stone Dip only the base of the lash extension into the adhesive Apply immediately to the natural lash — bonding occurs within 0.5 seconds Replace the glue drop every 10 minutes to maintain freshness and curing speed Professional Tips for Best Results Elite is recommended for lash artists already experienced with fast-drying adhesives — the 0.5-second cure leaves no room for repositioning Use a calibrated hygrometer to monitor room humidity — even small fluctuations affect cure time at this speed Work in a well-ventilated area to minimize fume buildup during extended sessions Store unopened bottles in the refrigerator to maximize shelf life After opening, store in a sealed thermo bag between sessions to slow degradation Storage and Safety Store in a cool, dark place away from direct sunlight and heat sources Keep bottle tightly sealed when not in use For professional external use only — intended for individual eyelash extension application Avoid contact with eyes; if contact occurs, rinse immediately with warm water and seek medical attention Keep out of reach of children Frequently Asked Questions Is Elite Lash Glue suitable for beginners? No. Elite is designed exclusively for expert and advanced lash technicians. Its 0.5-second dry time requires highly practiced, confident application with no time for adjustment. Beginners should start with a slower-drying adhesive. What is the difference between Elite and Royal lash glue? Elite has a faster dry time (0.5 seconds vs. 1 second), thinner viscosity, and is intended for expert-level artists. Royal has medium viscosity and a 1-second dry time, making it more accessible for a wider range of experienced technicians. What techniques is Elite compatible with? Elite works with both classic and volume eyelash extension techniques. How long does Elite Lash Glue last on lashes? Elite provides up to 8 weeks of retention under proper conditions when applied correctly and maintained with appropriate lash aftercare. Does Elite Lash Glue have strong fumes? No. Elite features a low-fume formula that minimizes vapor exposure for both the technician and client, making it more comfortable for long appointment sessions. Where is Elite Lash Glue made? Elite Eyelash Extension Glue is manufactured in South Korea. About Lovely US Lovely US is one of the largest professional lash supply brands in the world, serving over 5,000 lash artists across North America and tens of thousands globally. Every adhesive formula is developed and continuously refined over 8+ years to meet the performance demands of working professionals. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed on every order.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4381356884019</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extension Adhesive</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">0.5 second dry time, black adhesive, expert lash adhesive, eyelash adhesive, eyelash extension adhesive, Eyelash extension glue, eyelash extensions glue, eyelash glue, fast dry lash glue, fast-drying adhesive, Fastest eyelash extension glue, lash adhesive, lash glue, professional lash glue, professional lash supplies, Strongest Lash Glue, volume lash glue</param>
        <param name="Expiration Date" noFilter="true">10/21/2026</param>
        <param name="Drying speed" noFilter="true">0.5 Sec</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ELITE-GLUE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4381338370099" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/ideal-eyelash-extension-glue</url>
        <price>28</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>2</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Ideal_Glue_-9914_1e7b74da-5e0e-49a8-b82d-5f1ee250a7db.jpg?v=1762457161</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_Ideal_Glue_-9915_4180f66d-99a2-4b74-a6d2-5e9ff47ccbe1.jpg?v=1602333429</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/Ideal_on_Platform.png?v=1779825251</picture>
        <name>Ideal Eyelash Extension Glue – Universal Salon Adhesive, 1-Second Dry, 5 ml</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extension Adhesive</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEAL-GLUE</vendorCode>
        <description>Ideal Eyelash Extension Glue by Lovely US – 5 ml What is Ideal Lash Glue? Ideal Eyelash Extension Glue is a professional-grade, black lash adhesive manufactured by Lovely US. It features a 1-second drying time , 8-week retention , medium viscosity , high flexibility , minimal fumes , and a formaldehyde-free formula . It is compatible with classic, volume, and mega volume eyelash extension techniques. Ideal is the most universal professional salon adhesive in the Lovely US lineup — designed for advanced to expert lash technicians who work across multiple techniques and need a single, reliable adhesive that performs consistently in any lash room environment. Key Specifications Brand: Lovely US Volume: 5 ml Color: Black Drying time: 1 second Retention: Up to 8 weeks Viscosity: Medium Flexibility: High Fume level: Minimal Formula: Formaldehyde-free Compatible techniques: Classic, volume, mega volume Skill level: Advanced to expert lash technicians Country of origin: South Korea Why Lash Artists Choose Ideal 1-second dry time — Industry-standard speed that balances efficiency and control for advanced artists 8-week retention — Long-lasting bond that reduces client fill frequency and increases satisfaction High flexibility — Superior bond that moves naturally with lashes, ideal for active clients Medium viscosity — Smooth, precise consistency for detailed volume fan work and classic application Minimal fumes — Low evaporation formula for enhanced comfort during long sets Formaldehyde-free — Reduces irritation risk for both technician and client Universal technique compatibility — One adhesive for classic, volume, and mega volume — no switching between glues Proven formula — Refined over 8+ years of professional development and real-world feedback Optimal Working Conditions For consistent 1-second curing, maintain the following environment: Temperature: 66°F–77°F (18°C–23°C) Humidity: 40%–70% relative humidity Shelf life (unopened): 6 months from production date Shelf life (after opening): Use within 2 months for optimal performance How to Apply Ideal Lash Glue Shake the bottle well before every use to ensure consistent viscosity Dispense a small drop onto a glue palette or jade stone Dip only the base of the lash extension into the adhesive Apply to the natural lash for a secure bond Replace the glue drop every 10 minutes to maintain freshness and optimal curing speed Professional Tips for Best Results Ideal is the preferred choice for lash artists who offer multiple techniques and want one adhesive that performs across all of them High flexibility makes it especially well-suited for clients with oily skin or active lifestyles, where lash movement is a factor Use a calibrated hygrometer to monitor room humidity — consistent conditions are key to reliable 1-second curing Work in a well-ventilated area; the minimal fume formula makes extended sessions more comfortable Store unopened bottles in the refrigerator to extend shelf life After opening, store in a sealed thermo bag between sessions Storage and Safety Store in a cool, dark place away from direct sunlight and heat sources Keep bottle tightly sealed when not in use For professional external use only — intended for individual eyelash extension application Avoid contact with eyes; if contact occurs, rinse immediately with warm water and seek medical attention Keep out of reach of children Frequently Asked Questions What makes Ideal lash glue &quot;universal&quot;? Ideal is formulated to perform consistently across classic, volume, and mega volume techniques without needing to switch adhesives. Its medium viscosity and high flexibility make it adaptable to a wide range of lash styles, client types, and working environments. What is the difference between Ideal and Royal lash glue? Both have a 1-second dry time and medium viscosity, but Ideal offers higher flexibility and minimal fumes, making it the better choice for artists who prioritize client comfort and work across multiple techniques. Royal is the best-selling worldwide option with a strong track record across volume and classic applications. What is the difference between Ideal and Elite lash glue? Elite has a faster 0.5-second dry time and thinner viscosity, designed exclusively for expert-level artists. Ideal’s 1-second dry time and medium viscosity make it more controlled and accessible for advanced artists who want versatility over maximum speed. Is Ideal lash glue formaldehyde-free? Yes. Ideal Eyelash Extension Glue is formaldehyde-free, making it one of the safer professional adhesive options for both technician and client. How long does Ideal lash glue last on lashes? Ideal provides up to 8 weeks of retention under proper conditions when applied correctly and maintained with appropriate lash aftercare. Is Ideal suitable for sensitive clients? Ideal’s formaldehyde-free formula and minimal fume level make it a lower-irritation option compared to standard adhesives. However, for clients with known lash adhesive sensitivities, consider Lovely US Pure adhesive specifically formulated for sensitive eyes. Where is Ideal lash glue made? Ideal Eyelash Extension Glue is manufactured in South Korea. About Lovely US Lovely US is one of the largest professional lash supply brands in the world, serving over 5,000 lash artists across North America and tens of thousands globally. Every adhesive formula is developed and refined over 8+ years to meet the performance demands of working professionals. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed on every order.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4381338370099</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extension Adhesive</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">1 second dry time, black adhesive, eyelash adhesive, eyelash extension adhesive, Eyelash extension glue, eyelash extensions glue, eyelash glue, formaldehyde-free, formaldehyde-free lash glue, lash adhesive, lash glue, Marvel, professional lash glue, professional lash supplies, volume lash adhesive, volume lash glue</param>
        <param name="Expiration Date" noFilter="true">10/21/2026</param>
        <param name="Drying speed" noFilter="true">1 Second</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEAL-GLUE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9170118639893" available="false">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/lash-glue-booster</url>
        <price>15</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>6</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/GlueBooster1.webp?v=1762460111</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/GlueBooster2.jpg?v=1722353999</picture>
        <name>Lash Glue Booster for Eyelash Extensions</name>
        <typePrefix>Preparations</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>8U-8VDM-BXOZ</vendorCode>
        <description>Faster Bonds. Stronger Retention. Flawless Results. The Lovely US Lash Glue Booster is a professional-grade accelerator designed to optimize the polymerization of lash adhesive — giving you faster cure times, stronger bonds, and longer-lasting retention with every set. Applied before extension placement, it primes the natural lash surface by removing excess moisture and oils, creating the ideal conditions for maximum adhesive performance. Trusted by lash technicians who demand precision and consistency. How to Use Step 1 — Prep the lashes: Ensure natural lashes are clean and dry before starting. Step 2 — Apply the Booster: Using a microbrush, apply a thin, even layer of Booster along the natural lashes from base to tip. Step 3 — Allow to fully dry: Wait 30–60 seconds until completely dry before proceeding. Applying extensions over wet Booster can slow adhesive cure time. Step 4 — Begin extension placement: Proceed with your lash application as normal. The primed surface will promote faster bonding and stronger retention. Use sparingly — a thin layer is all you need. Storage &amp; Shelf Life Store at: 41°F – 77°F (5°C – 25°C), away from direct sunlight and heat sources. Keep tightly closed. Shelf life: 24 months unopened. After opening: Use within 6 months. Expiration date: 11/01/2026 Made in China. For professional use only.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9170118639893</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Preparations</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">adhesive accelerator, eyelash extensions, lash glue booster, lash retention, professional lash supplies</param>
        <param name="Scent" noFilter="true">Tropical Fruits</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">8U-8VDM-BXOZ</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="9170061361429" available="false">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/lash-glue-bonder</url>
        <price>15</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>5</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/GlueBonder.webp?v=1762460111</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/GlueBonder2.jpg?v=1722353865</picture>
        <name>Lash Glue Bonder for Eyelash Extensions</name>
        <typePrefix>Glue Bonder</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>GM-IYH8-47UM</vendorCode>
        <description>Stronger Bonds. Extended Retention. Professional Results. The Lovely US Lash Glue Bonder is a professional-grade formula engineered to maximize adhesion between natural lashes and eyelash extensions. By instantly curing the adhesive once the full set is placed, it locks in the bond, reduces fume exposure, and significantly extends retention — keeping your clients&apos; sets looking flawless for longer. A must-have finishing step in every lash technician&apos;s application routine. How to Use Step 1 — Complete the full set: Apply all lash extensions as normal before using the Bonder. Step 2 — Apply the Bonder: Once all extensions are placed, apply a small amount of Bonder to the base of the lash extensions using a microbrush. Work along the lash line evenly. Step 3 — Allow to cure: Wait 60–90 seconds for the Bonder to fully cure the adhesive. Fan gently to speed up the process. Step 4 — Final check: Inspect the set and ensure all bonds are secure before the client opens their eyes. Storage &amp; Shelf Life Store at: 41°F – 77°F (5°C – 25°C), away from direct sunlight and heat sources. Keep tightly closed. Shelf life: 24 months unopened. After opening: Use within 6 months. Made in China. For professional use only.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">9170061361429</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Glue Bonder</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Bonder, eyelash adhesive, eyelash extension adhesive, Eyelash extension glue, eyelash extensions, eyelash extensions glue, eyelash glue, Glue Bonder, lash adhesive, lash glue, lash glue bonder, lash retention, professional lash supplies</param>
        <param name="Expiration date" noFilter="true">10/1/2026</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">GM-IYH8-47UM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4418326560819" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/lash-wash</url>
        <price>12</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>6</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/1_6b6bb59f-a06c-4364-8f17-b323c86507b0.jpg?v=1776786577</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/2_7b155a7c-9ac6-40c2-b6fa-1a3166ea1ca1.jpg?v=1760466207</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lashwash.jpg?v=1760466207</picture>
        <name>Lash Wash Foaming Cleanser – Eyelash Extension Shampoo, Aloe, 50 ml</name>
        <typePrefix>Preparations</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>LASH-WASH-ALOE</vendorCode>
        <description>Lash Wash Foaming Cleanser by Lovely US – 50 ml | Aloe Scent What is Lash Wash? Lash Wash is a professional foaming eyelash extension cleanser manufactured by Lovely US. It is formulated with hyaluronic acid and amino acids to clean, hydrate, and condition lashes and eyelids before and after lash extension application. It removes eye makeup, adhesive residue, and adhesive fumes without weakening lash extension bonds. Lash Wash serves two critical roles in the lash extension process: pre-application preparation (removing oils and residue that reduce adhesive bonding) and post-application maintenance (breaking down adhesive fumes and keeping lashes clean between fills). Used consistently, it extends lash retention and improves client outcomes. Key Specifications Brand: Lovely Size: 50 ml Scent: Aloe Format: Foaming cleanser Key ingredients: Hyaluronic acid, amino acids pH: Balanced foaming formula Safe for: Eyelash extensions, natural lashes, eyelids Free From Lash Wash is formulated without the following ingredients, making it safe for sensitive skin and lash extension clients: Gluten-free Paraben-free Phthalate-free Ethylene oxide-free Betaine-free Sulfate-free Polyquaternium-free Artificial color-free Vegan &amp; cruelty-free Why Lash Artists Choose Lash Wash Extends lash retention — Removes natural oils and residue from lashes before application, improving adhesive bonding and prolonging extension life Breaks down adhesive fumes — Post-application use neutralizes cyanoacrylate fumes that can cause irritation and premature bond weakening Hydrates and nourishes — Hyaluronic acid and amino acids replenish moisture in lids and lashes, supporting healthier natural lash growth Non-irritating formula — Gentle enough for daily use on sensitive eyelids and around lash extension bonds Does not weaken bonds — Specifically formulated to clean without compromising lash extension adhesive integrity Clean ingredient profile — Free from 8 common irritants; vegan and cruelty-free pH balanced — Maintains the natural pH of the eye area for comfortable, safe cleansing When to Use Lash Wash Pre-application (in salon): Apply before lash extension service to remove natural oils, makeup residue, and environmental buildup from natural lashes. Clean lashes bond faster and hold longer — best results when followed by a lash primer before adhesive application. Post-application (client home care): Recommend to clients for daily or every-other-day cleansing to remove makeup, dust, and adhesive fume residue. Regular cleansing is the single most effective way clients can extend the life of their lash extensions between fills. How to Use Lash Wash Dispense one pump of Lash Wash directly onto a closed eyelid Using a clean makeup brush or lash cleansing brush, gently work the foam through lashes and across the eyelid Continue until all makeup, oil, and residue is fully cleansed Rinse lashes and eyelid thoroughly with water Pat dry gently — avoid rubbing, which can stress extension bonds Professional Tips Retail Lash Wash to clients as part of a lash aftercare kit — clients who cleanse regularly return for fills less frequently and with healthier natural lashes Use in combination with a lash primer before adhesive application for maximum retention improvement The aloe scent formula is gentle enough for clients with fragrance sensitivities Store at room temperature away from direct sunlight and heat Storage and Safety Store at room temperature away from direct sunlight and heat Keep pump sealed when not in use For external use only — avoid direct contact with eyes If contact occurs, rinse immediately with water Keep out of reach of children Frequently Asked Questions What is lash wash used for? Lash wash is a foaming cleanser used to clean eyelash extensions and natural lashes. It removes makeup, natural oils, and adhesive fume residue both before lash extension application (to improve bonding) and as part of daily client home care (to extend retention between fills). Can you use regular face wash on eyelash extensions? No. Regular face washes often contain oils, sulfates, or other ingredients that break down lash extension adhesive bonds. Lash Wash by Lovely US is specifically formulated to clean effectively without compromising adhesive integrity. How often should clients wash their eyelash extensions? Lash extensions should be cleaned every 1–3 days. Daily cleansing with a gentle, extension-safe cleanser like Lash Wash is the most effective way to extend retention and maintain lash health between salon visits. Is Lash Wash safe for sensitive eyes? Yes. Lash Wash is free from parabens, sulfates, phthalates, ethylene oxide, betaine, polyquaternium, artificial color, and gluten. It is vegan, cruelty-free, and pH balanced, making it suitable for sensitive eyelids and clients prone to irritation. Does lash wash remove eyelash extensions? No. Lash Wash is formulated to clean lashes without weakening adhesive bonds. It removes surface residue, oils, and makeup without dissolving the cyanoacrylate adhesive used in professional lash extensions. What ingredients are in Lash Wash? Lash Wash contains hyaluronic acid and amino acids as key active ingredients, with a pH-balanced foaming base. It is free from gluten, parabens, phthalates, ethylene oxide, betaine, sulfates, polyquaternium, and artificial color. Where is Lovely US Lash Wash made? Lash Wash is manufactured in Canada (Prince Edward Island). About Lovely US Lovely US is one of the largest professional lash supply brands in the world, serving over 5,000 lash artists across North America and tens of thousands globally. Every product is developed and refined over 8+ years to meet the performance demands of working professionals. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed on every order.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4418326560819</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Preparations</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelash extension cleanser, eyelash extension shampoo, foaming lash wash, lash cleanser, lash shampoo</param>
        <param name="Scent" noFilter="true">Aloe</param>
        <param name="Expiration" noFilter="true">11/01/2027</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">LASH-WASH-ALOE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="8909508215061" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/brown-eyelash-extensions-20-lines</url>
        <price>20</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/IMG-5680.png?v=1762457554</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/IMG-5676.jpg?v=1698893324</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/IMG-5675.jpg?v=1698893324</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/IMG-5677.jpg?v=1698893324</picture>
        <name>Brown Eyelash Extensions | C &amp; D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 7–17mm | 20 Lines | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>BROWN-C-007-7MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Brown Eyelash Extensions – Soft, Natural, Long-Lasting Designed for lash technicians who value a refined, natural finish. Our Brown Lash Extensions deliver a softer, more tender look than classic black — ideal for clients who want seamless, undetectable results as their natural lashes grow. Why Brown? Natural grow-out — the difference between extensions and natural lashes is barely noticeable over time Softer aesthetic — rich brown pigment creates a warmer, more natural look Versatile — perfect for classic, volume, and mega volume sets What&apos;s in the Tray 20 lines per tray — up to 13,000 lashes depending on thickness Available in C &amp; D curl , .07 &amp; .10 thickness , 7–17mm lengths High-quality fiber — even, elastic, and shape-retaining Quality You Can Trust Every palette is tested by Lovely&apos;s quality department. Our lashes are made from premium fiber that holds its shape through wear and doesn&apos;t deform during application.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">8909508215061</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">brown eyelash extensions, brown lashes, Classic Eyelash Extensions, Classic Lashes, Colored Eyelash Extensions, colored lashes, colorful eyelash extensions, colorful lashes, Creative eyelash extensions, Eyelash Extensions, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">.07, .10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">7 mm, 8 mm, 9 mm, 10 mm, 11 mm, 12 mm, 13 mm, 14 mm, 15 mm, 16 mm, 17 mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">BROWN-C-007-7MM, BROWN-C-007-8MM, BROWN-C-007-9MM, BROWN-C-007-10MM, BROWN-C-007-11MM, BROWN-C-007-12MM, BROWN-C-007-13MM, BROWN-C-007-14MM, BROWN-C-007-15MM, BROWN-C-010-7MM, BROWN-C-010-8MM, BROWN-C-010-9MM, BROWN-C-010-10MM, BROWN-C-010-11MM, BROWN-C-010-12MM, BROWN-C-010-13MM, BROWN-C-010-14MM, BROWN-C-010-15MM, BROWN-D-007-7MM, BROWN-D-007-8MM, +24 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">44</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="8568570904853" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/new-rili-eyelash-extensions-16-lines-m-curl</url>
        <price>10</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/f3f693330bb9f260753585679be23e8a_db32a95f-dc3b-46fb-a7d8-63f81c703174.webp?v=1762457381</picture>
        <name>Rili Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | Black | M Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 6–15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>RILI-M-007-6mm</vendorCode>
        <description>Premium Rili Eyelash Extensions - Professional M Curl Lashes Experience the difference with Rili by Lovely – the trusted choice of professional lash technicians worldwide. These premium eyelash extensions deliver exceptional quality, consistency, and ease of application for flawless lash sets every time. Why Lash Artists Love Rili Extensions: Superior Fiber Quality: Crafted from ultra-soft, high-quality synthetic fiber that mimics natural lashes perfectly Perfect M Curl: Industry-recognized curl pattern that creates beautiful, natural-looking volume and lift Vietnamese Craftsmanship: Premium production standards ensure consistent curl retention, uniform thickness, and perfectly tapered tips Optimal Tape Adhesion: Medium-tack tape allows easy removal and fan formation for both tape and manual techniques Smart Labeling System: Clearly marked by thickness, length, and curl – stay organized during multi-curl applications Clean Base Design: Minimal adhesive residue makes hand-made fan creation effortless Professional Results, Exceptional Value Rili eyelash extensions deliver salon-quality results without the premium price tag. Whether you&apos;re building classic sets or creating dramatic volume fans, these lashes offer the perfect balance of quality, performance, and affordability. 16 lines per tray | M Curl | Professional Grade Elevate your lash artistry with Rili – where quality meets value.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">8568570904853</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">M</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">6mm, 7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm, 15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">RILI-M-007-6mm, RILI-M-007-7mm, RILI-M-007-8mm, RILI-M-007-9mm, RILI-M-007-10mm, RILI-M-007-11mm, RILI-M-007-12mm, RILI-M-007-13mm, RILI-M-007-14mm, RILI-M-007-15mm, RILI-M-010-6mm, RILI-M-010-7mm, RILI-M-010-8mm, RILI-M-010-9mm, RILI-M-010-10mm, RILI-M-010-11mm, RILI-M-010-12mm, RILI-M-010-13mm, RILI-M-010-14mm, RILI-M-010-15mm</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">20</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="8090589987093" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/copy-of-new-rili-eyelash-extensions-16-lines</url>
        <price>10</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/RiliMix.webp?v=1762457278</picture>
        <name>Rili Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | MIX | Black | B C C+ CC D L M Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 6–15mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>RILI-B-007-6-13mm</vendorCode>
        <description>RILI — Premium Vietnamese Eyelash Extensions for Professional Volume Work Discover exceptional quality with Rili eyelash extensions . Crafted from soft, high-quality fiber with industry-recognized curls trusted by professional lash masters worldwide, Rili delivers the perfect combination of reliability, performance, and value. Each 16-line mix palette provides everything you need for stunning volume lash applications. Why Lash Artists Choose Rili Rili is the go-to choice for professional lash technicians who demand consistent quality and versatile performance. The premium Vietnamese production ensures stable curls, uniform thickness, and perfectly even lash tips that make every application seamless and professional. Premium Quality Features Premium Vietnamese Production: Guaranteed quality with stable curls, consistent thickness throughout the palette, and perfectly even lash tips Optimal Tape Adhesion: Medium-stick tape allows easy removal and fan formation for both tape and manual techniques Clear Labeling System: Each row clearly marked by thickness, length, and curl for seamless multi-curl procedures Manual Lash Maker Friendly: Adhesive layer won&apos;t transfer to lash base, ensuring clean fan formation 16 Lines Per Tray: Complete mix palette contains all essential lengths for professional lash extension work Available in Multiple Stylish Shades Complete your lash collection with Black , Choco , Cookie , and Toffee to offer clients versatile color options for every look and preference. Professional Application Remove the desired number of lashes from the strip using precision tweezers. Create single lash applications or form custom volume fans according to your preferred technique. Use with professional-grade lash extension adhesive following manufacturer instructions. Product Specifications Lines: 16 lines per tray Material: Soft, high-quality synthetic fiber Origin: Made in Vietnam Use: For external professional use only Storage &amp; Safety Store at room temperature away from direct sunlight and heating sources. Keep out of reach of children. For professional use only. Elevate your lash artistry with Rili — where superior quality meets affordability for professional results without compromise.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">8090589987093</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelash extensions, lash artist supplies, professional lash supplies, rili lashes, volume lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">B, C, C+, CC, D, L, M</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">6-13mm, 8-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">RILI-B-007-6-13mm, RILI-B-010-6-13mm, RILI-C-007-6-13mm, RILI-C-007-8-15mm, RILI-C-010-6-13mm, RILI-C-010-8-15mm, RILI-C+-007-6-13mm, RILI-C+-007-8-15mm, RILI-C+-010-6-13mm, RILI-C+-010-8-15mm, RILI-CC-007-6-13mm, RILI-CC-007-8-15mm, RILI-CC-010-6-13mm, RILI-CC-010-8-15mm, RILI-D-007-6-13mm, RILI-D-007-8-15mm, RILI-D-010-6-13mm, RILI-D-010-8-15mm, RILI-L-007-6-13mm, RILI-L-007-8-15mm, +6 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">26</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="8090550272277" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/copy-of-new-lashy-eyelash-extensions-red-16-lines</url>
        <price>8</price>
        <oldprice>12</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/f3f693330bb9f260753585679be23e8a.webp?v=1762457278</picture>
        <name>Rili Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | Black | C C+ D L Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 5–16mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>RILI-C-007-5mm</vendorCode>
        <description>Rili by Lovely - Premium Eyelash Extensions for Professional Lash Artists Rili eyelash extensions deliver exceptional quality and performance for professional lash technicians. Crafted from soft, high-quality synthetic fiber, these individual lash extensions feature industry-recognized curls trusted by master lash artists worldwide. Key Features: Premium Vietnamese Production - Superior quality control ensures consistent curl retention, uniform thickness across the palette, and perfectly tapered lash tips Optimal Adhesive Balance - Medium-tack tape allows easy removal and fan formation for both tape and manual techniques Professional-Grade Fiber - Soft, lightweight material provides comfortable wear and natural-looking results Clear Labeling System - Each strip clearly marked with thickness, length, and curl type for efficient workflow during application Versatile Application - Ideal for volume lash extensions, classic sets, and hybrid techniques Manual Technique Friendly - Adhesive layer won&apos;t transfer to lash base, ensuring clean fan creation Why Choose Rili Lash Extensions? Rili combines professional-quality performance with exceptional value. The consistent curl stability and precise manufacturing standards make these extensions perfect for experienced lash technicians and those building their lash business. Each 16-line tray provides reliable, long-lasting results that keep clients coming back. Perfect for: Volume lashes, classic lash extensions, hybrid sets, professional lash artists, lash technicians, salon use</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">8090550272277</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, C+, D, L</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">5mm, 6mm, 7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm, 15mm, 16mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">RILI-C-007-5mm, RILI-C-007-6mm, RILI-C-007-7mm, RILI-C-007-8mm, RILI-C-007-9mm, RILI-C-007-10mm, RILI-C-007-11mm, RILI-C-007-12mm, RILI-C-007-13mm, RILI-C-007-14mm, RILI-C-007-15mm, RILI-C-010-5mm, RILI-C-010-6mm, RILI-C-010-7mm, RILI-C-010-8mm, RILI-C-010-9mm, RILI-C-010-10mm, RILI-C-010-11mm, RILI-C-010-12mm, RILI-C-010-13mm, +66 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">86</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="8080017981717" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/new-lashy-eyelash-extensions-red-16-lines-bend-d-l-m</url>
        <price>8</price>
        <oldprice>12</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LashyRed_7adc1125-c9eb-4989-842f-6cf1b55a75cd.webp?v=1762457276</picture>
        <name>Lashy Red Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | Black | D L M Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 6–15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>RED-D-007-6mm</vendorCode>
        <description>Lashy by Lovely – Professional Lash Extensions Built for Speed &amp; Precision Lashy lashes are engineered for lash technicians who demand consistency, control, and a flawless finish. With a rich black color and glossy surface, these extensions deliver a polished look that clients love. Why Lash Techs Choose Lashy Ideal tape stickiness — fans form effortlessly without breaking, perfect for both tape-in and handmade fan techniques Clean adhesive layer — no residue at the lash base, so fans form smoothly every time Clear labeling — each strip is labeled by thickness, length, and bend so you stay organized mid-appointment Cost-effective — 16 lines per tray maximizes your yield and improves procedure profitability Specs Curl: D, L, M Thickness: 0.07 / 0.10 Length: 6–15mm Lines: 16 per tray Finish: Glossy black</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">8080017981717</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes, Volume eyelash extensions, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">D, L, M</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">6mm, 7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm, 15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">RED-D-007-6mm, RED-D-007-7mm, RED-D-007-8mm, RED-D-007-9mm, RED-D-007-10mm, RED-D-007-11mm, RED-D-007-12mm, RED-D-007-13mm, RED-D-007-14mm, RED-D-007-15mm, RED-D-010-6mm, RED-D-010-7mm, RED-D-010-8mm, RED-D-010-9mm, RED-D-010-10mm, RED-D-010-11mm, RED-D-010-12mm, RED-D-010-13mm, RED-D-010-14mm, RED-D-010-15mm, +40 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">60</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="8079844475157" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/new-lashy-eyelash-extensions-red-16-lines</url>
        <price>8</price>
        <oldprice>12</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LashyRed.webp?v=1762457276</picture>
        <name>Lashy Red Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | Black | C C+ CC Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 6–15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>RED-C-007-6MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Lashy by Lovely - Premium 16-Line Eyelash Extensions Elevate your lash artistry with Lashy professional eyelash extensions, engineered for flawless volume lash applications. These premium individual lash extensions feature a rich black pigment and glossy finish that creates stunning, natural-looking results your clients will love. Why Lash Artists Choose Lashy: Superior Quality Lashes: Deep black pigment with a luxurious glossy surface delivers a natural, elegant look that lasts Optimized for Volume Lashes: Perfectly balanced tape stickiness ideal for both tape-in technique and manual fan creation Effortless Fan Formation: Create beautiful volume fans instantly without breaking or splitting - perfect for Russian volume and mega volume techniques Clean Application Every Time: Advanced adhesive layer prevents transfer to lash base, ensuring seamless fan formation and precise placement Professional Organization: Each tray clearly labeled by thickness (0.07mm, 0.10mm), length (6-15mm), and curl (C, C+, CC) for efficient workflow 16-Line Tray Design: More lashes per tray means better value and fewer tray changes during application Cost-Effective Pricing: Premium quality at competitive prices maximizes your service profitability Perfect For: Classic lash extensions Volume lash sets (2D-6D) Russian volume and mega volume techniques Hybrid lash applications Lash fills and touch-ups Technical Specifications: Curl Types: C Curl, C+ Curl, CC Curl Thickness: 0.07mm, 0.10mm Lengths: 6mm, 7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm, 15mm Tray Format: 16 lines per tray Finish: Glossy black Lashy eyelash extensions are designed for professional lash technicians who demand quality, consistency, and value in every lash application. Whether you&apos;re creating classic sets or intricate volume fans, Lashy delivers the performance you need to build your lash business.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">8079844475157</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">0.07mm lashes, 0.10mm lashes, 16 line lash tray, C curl lashes, CC curl lashes, classic lash extensions, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lash extension supplies, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes, professional lash supplies, Russian volume lashes, volume lash fans, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, C+, CC</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">6mm, 7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm, 15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">RED-C-007-6MM, RED-C-007-7MM, RED-C-007-8MM, RED-C-007-9MM, RED-C-007-10MM, RED-C-007-11MM, RED-C-007-12MM, RED-C-007-13MM, RED-C-007-14MM, RED-C-010-6MM, RED-C-010-7MM, RED-C-010-8MM, RED-C-010-9MM, RED-C-010-10MM, RED-C-010-11MM, RED-C-010-12MM, RED-C-010-13MM, RED-C-010-14MM, RED-C+-007-6MM, RED-C+-007-7MM, +36 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">56</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="8079035728149" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/new-lashy-eyelash-extensions-red-16-lines-mix</url>
        <price>8</price>
        <oldprice>12</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LashyRedMix.webp?v=1762457275</picture>
        <name>Lashy Red Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | MIX | Black | C C+ CC D L M Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 4–15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>RED-C-007-4-9MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Lashy by Lovely — Professional Eyelash Extensions Rich black, glossy finish lashes engineered for precision and speed. Designed for lash technicians who demand consistency every set. Perfect fan formation — average-tack tape holds fans without breaking or leaving adhesive residue on the base Labeled by thickness, length &amp; bend — no mix-ups mid-procedure, even when using multiple curls MIX palette logic — each mix continues the previous, so zero unused lengths Available in C, C+, CC, D, L, M curls | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 thickness | 4–15mm lengths Cost-effective per tray — maximizes your margin per procedure</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">8079035728149</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Classic Eyelash Extensions, Eyelash Extensions, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, C+, CC, D, L, M</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">4-9mm, 5-10mm, 7-12mm, 10-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">RED-C-007-4-9MM, RED-C-007-5-10MM, RED-C-007-7-12MM, RED-C-007-10-15MM, RED-C-010-4-9MM, RED-C-010-5-10MM, RED-C-010-7-12MM, RED-C-010-10-15MM, RED-C+-007-5-10MM, RED-C+-007-7-12MM, RED-C+-007-10-15MM, RED-C+-010-5-10MM, RED-C+-010-7-12MM, RED-C+-010-10-15MM, RED-CC-007-7-12MM, RED-CC-007-10-15MM, RED-CC-010-7-12MM, RED-CC-010-10-15MM, RED-D-007-5-10MM, RED-D-007-7-12MM, +16 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">36</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="7994836877589" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/new-lashy-eyelash-extensions-6-lines-mix</url>
        <price>2</price>
        <oldprice>6</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_5e21f352-5941-47dd-b493-cea8ec0f9711.jpg?v=1762457255</picture>
        <name>Lashy Green Eyelash Extensions | 6 Lines | MIX | Black | C D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 8–16mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>GREEN-C-007-8-12MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Lashy by Lovely – Professional Volume Lashes Designed for lash artists who demand precision and efficiency, the LASHY series features ultra-soft fibers that create natural, expressive volume with every application. Revolutionary Foil Base Technology Effortless tape removal – strips lift cleanly from the tray every time Restickable design – reposition tape multiple times without losing adhesion No residue or marks – keeps your workspace clean and professional Faster application – spend less time prepping, more time creating Premium Quality Features Rich, deep black color with a subtle, natural-looking sheen Clear labeling by thickness, length, and curl – stay organized during multi-curl sets Soft, lightweight fibers for comfortable, long-lasting wear Professional-grade quality at a price that improves your profit margins Specifications Format: 6-line mix tray Available Curls: C, D Thickness Options: 0.07mm, 0.10mm Length Range: 8mm – 16mm Trusted by professional lash technicians across North America for consistent results and superior value.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">7994836877589</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">8-12mm, 10-14mm, 13-16mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">GREEN-C-007-8-12MM, GREEN-C-007-10-14MM, GREEN-C-010-8-12MM, GREEN-C-010-13-16MM, GREEN-D-007-8-12MM, GREEN-D-007-13-16MM, GREEN-D-010-8-12MM, GREEN-D-010-10-14MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">8</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="7994808762645" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/new-lashy-eyelash-extensions-16-lines-mix</url>
        <price>4</price>
        <oldprice>12</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/3032b3d805d2faf60b20d3bce9e6f57e.webp?v=1762457255</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/cfe78eccca87d781855f5ed5a78ebdbb.webp?v=1668116356</picture>
        <name>Lashy Green Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | MIX | Black | C C+ CC D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 4–15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>GREEN-C-007-4-9MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Lashy by Lovely – Professional Volume Lash Extensions Why Lash Artists Choose Lashy The Lashy series features premium, softer fiber technology engineered for natural-looking volume and effortless application. Each 16-line mixed tray delivers consistent curl retention and a rich, moderately glossy black finish that photographs beautifully. Revolutionary Foil Base Technology Experience the difference with our innovative foil base system: Effortless Tape Removal – Lashes lift cleanly from the tray every time Reusable Adhesion – Restick your tape multiple times without losing grip Zero Residue – No paper marks, prints, or sticky mess on your tray Faster Application – Streamline your workflow and reduce appointment time Professional Features Smart Labeling System: Each tape is clearly marked with thickness, length, and curl – perfect for multi-curl techniques and complex volume sets. Rich Black Pigment: Deep, consistent color with moderate shine for a polished, professional finish. Cost-Effective: Premium quality at a price point that protects your margins and increases profitability per client. Perfect For ✓ Classic and volume lash applications ✓ Natural, wispy, and dramatic styles ✓ Experienced artists and students alike ✓ Clients seeking long-lasting, comfortable wear Trusted by professional lash artists across North America. Join thousands who&apos;ve made Lashy their go-to extension.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">7994808762645</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, C+, CC, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">4-9mm, 5-10mm, 7-12mm, 10-15mm, 9-12mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">GREEN-C-007-4-9MM, GREEN-C-007-5-10MM, GREEN-C-007-7-12MM, GREEN-C-007-10-15MM, GREEN-C-010-4-9MM, GREEN-C-010-5-10MM, GREEN-C-010-7-12MM, GREEN-C-010-10-15MM, GREEN-C+-007-4-9MM, GREEN-C+-007-5-10MM, GREEN-C+-007-7-12MM, GREEN-C+-007-9-12MM, GREEN-C+-007-10-15MM, GREEN-C+-010-4-9MM, GREEN-C+-010-5-10MM, GREEN-C+-010-7-12MM, GREEN-C+-010-9-12MM, GREEN-C+-010-10-15MM, GREEN-CC-007-4-9MM, GREEN-CC-007-5-10MM, +18 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">38</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="7993679675669" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/new-lashy-eyelash-extensions-16-lines</url>
        <price>5</price>
        <oldprice>12</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/b45160bc75980792ccd4f0d55eea597b.webp?v=1762457253</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/ed99e5593635fb5d06772a7f4668257d.webp?v=1668034133</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/IMG_7592.png?v=1675275006</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/IMG_7593.png?v=1675275025</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/IMG_7594.png?v=1675275042</picture>
        <name>Lashy Green Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | Black | C D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 5–15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>GREEN-C-007-5mm</vendorCode>
        <description>Lashy by Lovely Premium Eyelash Extensions Designed for Professional Lash Artists The LASHY series delivers a softer, more natural fiber that creates beautifully expressive lash sets your clients will love. Engineered for efficiency and precision, these extensions help you work faster while achieving flawless results. Revolutionary Foil Base Technology Experience the difference with our innovative foil base system: Effortless tape removal – strips lift cleanly from the tray every time Reusable adhesion – restick tape multiple times without losing grip Zero residue – no marks, paper prints, or sticky mess on your tray Streamlined workflow – fast, clean, and incredibly convenient for back-to-back appointments Professional-Grade Quality Rich black color with moderate glossiness for a natural yet defined look Clear labeling by thickness, length, and curl – stay organized when working with multiple dimensions Soft, lightweight fiber that&apos;s comfortable for clients and easy to apply 16 lines per tray – excellent value that increases your per-client profitability Cost-Effective for Your Business Maximize your margins without compromising quality. Lashy extensions offer professional performance at a price point that boosts the cost-effectiveness of every lash service. Trusted by lash artists across North America for consistent quality and reliable results.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">7993679675669</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">5mm, 6mm, 7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm, 15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">GREEN-C-007-5mm, GREEN-C-007-6mm, GREEN-C-007-7mm, GREEN-C-007-8mm, GREEN-C-007-9mm, GREEN-C-007-10mm, GREEN-C-007-11mm, GREEN-C-007-12mm, GREEN-C-007-13mm, GREEN-C-007-14mm, GREEN-C-007-15mm, GREEN-C-010-5mm, GREEN-C-010-6mm, GREEN-C-010-7mm, GREEN-C-010-8mm, GREEN-C-010-9mm, GREEN-C-010-10mm, GREEN-C-010-11mm, GREEN-C-010-12mm, GREEN-C-010-13mm, +22 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">42</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="6805826666547" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/ideal-eyelash-extensions-20-lines-new-variants</url>
        <price>20</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_241d7837-327d-45a8-b75a-fa3896a2d9dd.jpg?v=1762457238</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_0d6e8387-c5d3-42e1-b5c6-00ab77e32726.jpg?v=1661909854</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart2_60169943-6758-44f0-9e54-e670dcf7c3f7.jpg?v=1661909854</picture>
        <name>Ideal Eyelash Extensions | 20 Lines | Black | CC M Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 7–14mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEAL-CC-007-7MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Versatile CC/M Curl Eyelash Extensions for Natural to Dramatic Styles Discover the ultimate flexibility with our Ideal Eyelash Extensions in CC/M Curl – the go-to choice for lash professionals who create everything from natural everyday looks to glamorous volume sets. Premium Quality Features Ideal eyelash extensions are made of high-quality fiber, are very elastic and have a round basis on the cut. Ideal lashes have a soft natural shine and short tips. They are ideal for classic, hybrid, volume, and mega volume lashing. Why Professionals Love CC/M Curl Extensions Dual Curl Versatility: CC and M curls offer the perfect balance between natural lift and eye-opening drama, suitable for most eye shapes 20 Lines Per Tray: Professional-sized tray with up to 13,000 lashes for exceptional value and multiple client services Soft, Natural Appearance: Premium synthetic fibers with a subtle shine that looks beautiful and feels weightless Exceptional Retention: Engineered for superior bonding and long-lasting wear that keeps clients coming back Multi-Technique Compatible: Perfect for classic, hybrid, volume, and mega volume lash applications with consistent results Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Professional Quality You Can Trust Each lash is precision-crafted to maintain curl consistency and flexibility throughout the application process. Ideal for creating customized lash designs that enhance every client&apos;s natural beauty. Trusted by lash artists nationwide. Deliver stunning, reliable results with extensions designed for professional excellence.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">6805826666547</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">CC curl lashes, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, hybrid lashes, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, Ideal lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lash artist supplies, lashes, Lovely Lashes, M curl lashes, professional extensions</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">CC, M</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEAL-CC-007-7MM, IDEAL-CC-007-8MM, IDEAL-CC-007-9MM, IDEAL-CC-007-10MM, IDEAL-CC-007-11MM, IDEAL-CC-007-12MM, IDEAL-CC-007-13MM, IDEAL-CC-007-14MM, IDEAL-M-007-7MM, IDEAL-M-007-8MM, IDEAL-M-007-9MM, IDEAL-M-007-10MM, IDEAL-M-007-11MM, IDEAL-M-007-12MM, IDEAL-M-010-8MM, IDEAL-M-010-7MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">16</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="6540106104883" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/royal-eyelash-extensions-l-curl</url>
        <price>14.45</price>
        <oldprice>17</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1384_56dad0c8-c170-4f5a-ba3a-9137f2252c37.jpg?v=1762457223</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9926_84740000-5ae6-4fd6-a255-8fbacedb9927.jpg?v=1615308486</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9929_010325da-0c58-4d03-9c2d-1f7de2da6079.jpg?v=1615308486</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart_49e8d02c-ca3d-4b97-be15-1f76b8ff0789.jpg?v=1615308486</picture>
        <name>Royal Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | Black | L Curl | 0.07 | 7–14mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ROYAL-L-007-7MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Royal Eyelash Extensions - 16 Lines L Curl Achieve the perfect lifted look with our Royal L Curl Eyelash Extensions. Designed for professional lash technicians, this 16-line tray delivers natural-looking lift and opens the eye beautifully for clients with straight or downward-pointing natural lashes. L Curl Advantages Natural Lift Effect: L curl provides subtle elevation without appearing overly dramatic—ideal for clients seeking an everyday elegant look Straight Base Design: Flat base adheres perfectly to natural lashes, maximizing retention and bond strength Eye-Opening Results: Lifts and opens hooded or deep-set eyes while maintaining a soft, natural appearance Versatile Application: Works beautifully for classic, volume, and hybrid lash techniques Premium Fiber Quality: Maintains curl integrity and rich black color throughout wear What&apos;s Included In this 16 line tray there are up to 10,500 lashes depending on their thickness. Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Perfect For Clients with straight natural lashes, hooded eyes, or those who want a lifted look without extreme curl. The L curl is your go-to for natural lash lifts that photograph beautifully and feel weightless. Professional Features: 16 organized lines for efficient selection, consistent thickness across all lengths, easy-release adhesive strips for smooth pickup. Join thousands of lash artists who trust Royal Extensions for predictable, gorgeous results appointment after appointment.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">6540106104883</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely US Lashes, Royal Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">L</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ROYAL-L-007-7MM, ROYAL-L-007-8MM, ROYAL-L-007-9MM, ROYAL-L-007-10MM, ROYAL-L-007-11MM, ROYAL-L-007-12MM, ROYAL-L-007-13MM, ROYAL-L-007-14MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">8</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="6540103909427" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/ideal-eyelash-extensions-l-curl</url>
        <price>8</price>
        <oldprice>20</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions_1a757e1f-575d-44b4-94cc-f27dcd58d1ca.jpg?v=1762457223</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1314_e55b90c3-3147-433e-b9f1-dd0c4263c88a.jpg?v=1615307434</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart2_0a1df904-3909-40f0-93f6-5a33a3bbc048.jpg?v=1615307434</picture>
        <name>Reduced Pricing | Ideal Eyelash Extensions | 20 Lines | L Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 &amp; 0.12 &amp; 0.15 &amp; 0.18 &amp; 0.20 | 7–15mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEAL-L-007-7MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Ideal Eyelash Extensions - 20 Lines L Curl Transform your lash artistry with our Ideal Eyelash Extensions in L Curl – the professional&apos;s choice for creating stunning lifted lash sets that last. Designed specifically for lash technicians who demand quality and consistency. Why Lash Artists Choose Ideal L Curl Extensions Perfect L Curl Shape: Ideal for clients with downward-facing natural lashes or hooded eyes, creating an instant lift without the need for excessive curling 20 Lines Per Tray: Maximum value with up to 13,000 premium lashes per tray for multiple client applications Soft Natural Shine: Luxurious matte-black finish that mimics natural lashes while maintaining professional durability Superior Retention: High-quality synthetic fibers engineered for long-lasting wear and minimal shedding Easy Application: Consistent curl pattern and flexible base for seamless application in classic, hybrid, and volume techniques Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Professional Specifications Each tray contains precisely crafted lashes that maintain their curl integrity throughout the entire wear period. Compatible with all professional lash adhesives and perfect for building customized lash maps. Made for professionals, trusted by lash artists. Elevate every client&apos;s look with extensions that deliver flawless results appointment after appointment.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">6540103909427</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, Ideal lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">L</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10, 0.12, 0.15, 0.18, 0.20</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm, 15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEAL-L-007-7MM, IDEAL-L-007-8MM, IDEAL-L-007-9MM, IDEAL-L-007-10MM, IDEAL-L-007-11MM, IDEAL-L-007-12MM, IDEAL-L-007-13MM, IDEAL-L-007-14MM, IDEAL-L-007-15MM, IDEAL-L-010-8MM, IDEAL-L-010-9MM, IDEAL-L-010-10MM, IDEAL-L-010-11MM, IDEAL-L-010-12MM, IDEAL-L-010-13MM, IDEAL-L-010-14MM, IDEAL-L-010-15MM, IDEAL-L-012-8MM, IDEAL-L-012-9MM, IDEAL-L-012-10MM, +29 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">49</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4647746142259" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/ideal-eyelash-extensions-6-line-mix</url>
        <price>6</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1335.jpg?v=1762457195</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1340.jpg?v=1597505182</picture>
        <name>Ideal Eyelash Extensions | 6 Lines | MIX | Black | C D Curl | 0.12 &amp; 0.15 | 8–14mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEAL-C-012-10-14MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Compact 6 Line Mix Eyelash Extensions for Targeted Applications Introducing our Ideal Eyelash Extensions 6 Line Mix – the perfect starter tray or refill option for lash professionals who need essential lengths without excess inventory. Why Choose the 6 Line Mix Essential Length Selection: Carefully curated mix of the most popular lengths for everyday lash applications Compact &amp; Efficient: Smaller tray size ideal for mobile lash artists, beginners, or as a backup supply Budget-Friendly Option: Professional quality at an accessible price point without compromising on performance Premium Synthetic Fibers: Same high-quality materials as our full-size trays with soft texture and natural shine Versatile Application: Suitable for classic, hybrid, and light volume lash techniques Ideal for Every Lash Professional Whether you&apos;re building your lash kit, restocking popular lengths, or working on-the-go, the 6 Line Mix delivers professional results in a convenient format. Quality you trust, size that works. Get professional-grade extensions tailored to your specific needs.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4647746142259</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.12, 0.15</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">10-14mm, 8-11mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEAL-C-012-10-14MM, IDEAL-C-012-8-11MM, IDEAL-C-015-10-14MM, IDEAL-C-015-8-11MM, IDEAL-D-015-10-14MM, IDEAL-D-015-8-11MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">6</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4647744995379" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/creative-eyelash-extensions-mixture-20-line-mix</url>
        <price>11</price>
        <oldprice>20</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1297.jpg?v=1762457195</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9936.jpg?v=1603487167</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1301.jpg?v=1597418981</picture>
        <name>Creative Colorful Eyelash Extensions – 20 Line Mix | C &amp; D Curl |</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>CREATIVE-C-007-8-15MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Creative Colorful Eyelash Extensions – 20 Line Mix for Bold, Unique Looks Elevate your lash artistry with our Creative Colorful Eyelash Extensions 20 Line Mix – the go-to choice for lash technicians who want to offer vibrant, one-of-a-kind sets that keep clients coming back. Why Lash Technicians Choose Creative Colorful Lashes Accent or Full-Color Sets: Use as bold accent lashes or create full colorful sets – mix freely for completely unique looks 20 Lines of Variety: Up to 13,000 lashes per palette for maximum value and creative flexibility High-Quality Synthetic Fiber: Light, elastic, and deformation-resistant during application and throughout wear Consistent Curl Pattern: Uniform curl across all lengths for predictable, beautiful results every time 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed: Every palette quality-tested by Lovely Length Guide 8mm–9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm–12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of the eye for a natural look 13mm–14mm: Creates a bold, dramatic look 15mm: Very bold length – best suited for clients with strong natural lashes Thickness Guide 0.07mm: Most popular for volume sets Perfect for Creative Lash Artists Designed for technicians who want to push boundaries and offer clients something truly special. Mix colors, create accents, or go full vibrant – the Creative 20 Line Mix gives you the palette to do it all. Stand out. Create boldly. The Creative 20 Line Mix is your toolkit for unforgettable lash sets.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4647744995379</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">accent lashes, colored extensions, Colored Eyelash Extensions, colored lashes, colorful eyelash extensions, colorful lash extensions, colorful lashes, creative lashes, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely US</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">8-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">CREATIVE-C-007-8-15MM, CREATIVE-D-007-8-15MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">2</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4632724996147" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/brown-eyelash-extensions-6-line-mix</url>
        <price>5</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1349.jpg?v=1762457192</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9899_54a7be30-06a6-415d-bdf3-a7053c736c85.jpg?v=1603487070</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9934_5af071e0-84e6-401e-a3ba-743b13df6cba.jpg?v=1603487076</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1352.jpg?v=1597369830</picture>
        <name>Brown Eyelash Extensions | 6 Lines | MIX | C D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 8–14mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>BROWN-C-007-8-11MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Brown Eyelash Extensions – 6 Line Mix for a Natural, Seamless Look Elevate your lash artistry with our Brown Eyelash Extensions 6 Line Mix – the go-to choice for lash technicians who want to deliver soft, natural-looking results that clients love and keep coming back for. Why Lash Technicians Choose Brown Eyelash Extensions Rich Brown Pigment: Creates a softer, more tender look compared to black – perfect for clients who prefer a natural aesthetic Seamless Grow-Out: As natural lashes grow, the difference between extensions and natural lashes is nearly imperceptible – extensions look fresh longer 6-Line Tray: Up to 4,000 lashes per palette depending on thickness – great value for targeted sets Premium Quality Fiber: Light, elastic, and deformation-resistant during application and throughout wear 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed: Every palette quality-tested by Lovely Same-Day Shipping: Orders placed before 1PM ET (Mon–Fri) ship the same day Free US Shipping on orders over $100 Length Guide 8mm–11mm: Ideal for the inner and outer corners – creates a natural, everyday look 10mm–14mm: Most commonly used for the center of the eye – adds definition without drama Thickness Guide 0.07mm: Most popular for volume sets 0.10mm: Used for volume sets with slightly more weight Perfect for Natural Beauty Enthusiasts Designed for technicians who specialize in soft, understated glamour. Brown extensions are the secret weapon for clients who want to look polished without looking overdone. Natural. Seamless. Beautiful. The Brown 6 Line Mix is your toolkit for effortlessly elegant lash sets.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4632724996147</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">brown eyelash extensions, brown lash extensions, brown lashes, Classic Eyelash Extensions, Classic Lashes, Colored Eyelash Extensions, colored lashes, colorful eyelash extensions, colorful lashes, Creative eyelash extensions, Eyelash Extensions, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes, natural lash extensions</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">8-11mm, 10-14mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">BROWN-C-007-8-11MM, BROWN-C-007-10-14MM, BROWN-C-010-8-11MM, BROWN-C-010-10-14MM, BROWN-D-007-8-11MM, BROWN-D-007-10-14MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">8</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4632720343091" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/brown-eyelash-extensions-20-line-mix</url>
        <price>10</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1326-2.jpg?v=1762457190</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9899.jpg?v=1603487040</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9934.jpg?v=1603487037</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1330_8ded4cbb-a0e2-4ff2-8879-68e8dfd3de83.jpg?v=1597369059</picture>
        <name>Brown Eyelash Extensions | MIX 20 Lines | C C+ CC D L Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 | 8–15mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>BROWN-C-007-8-15MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Brown Eyelash Extensions – 20 Line Mix for Professional Lash Artists Elevate your lash artistry with our Brown Eyelash Extensions - 20 Line Mix , the go-to choice for lash technicians who want a softer, more natural alternative to classic black. Rich brown pigment creates a tender, luminous look that blends seamlessly with natural lashes. Why Professionals Love Brown Extensions 20 Lines of Premium Lashes: Full professional tray with up to 13,000 high-quality extensions for multiple client applications Natural Brown Pigment: Softer than black — ideal for fair-skinned clients, blondes, and redheads who want a natural finish Longer-Lasting Look: As natural lashes grow, the difference between extensions and natural lashes is nearly imperceptible Superior Quality Fibers: Soft, lightweight synthetic lashes with a natural matte finish and excellent retention Multi-Technique Ready: Perfect for classic sets, hybrid designs, and volume fan creation Length Guide 8mm–9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm–12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of the eye for a natural look 13mm–14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm+: Very bold length — should not be used unless natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume Professional-Grade Quality Each lash is precision-manufactured and thoroughly tested by the Lovely US quality department. Perfectly even, elastic, and shape-retaining — these extensions perform appointment after appointment without deforming. The natural choice for lash artists who want softer, stunning results. Build your reputation on quality that keeps clients coming back.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4632720343091</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">brown eyelash extensions, brown lashes, Classic Eyelash Extensions, Classic Lashes, Colored Eyelash Extensions, colored lashes, colorful eyelash extensions, colorful lashes, Creative eyelash extensions, Eyelash Extensions, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Lovely US Lashes</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, C+, CC, D, L</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">8-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">BROWN-C-007-8-15MM, BROWN-C-010-8-15MM, BROWN-C+-007-8-15MM, BROWN-C+-010-8-15MM, BROWN-CC-007-8-15MM, BROWN-CC-010-8-15MM, BROWN-D-007-8-15MM, BROWN-D-010-8-15MM, BROWN-L-007-8-15MM, BROWN-L-010-8-15MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">10</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4632682397747" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/creative-eyelash-extensions-6-lines</url>
        <price>5</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1342.jpg?v=1762457190</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1346.jpg?v=1597369657</picture>
        <name>Creative Colorful Eyelash Extensions – 6 Line Tray | C &amp; D Curl |</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>CREATIVE-6LINES-C-007-10MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Creative Colorful Eyelash Extensions by Lovely US Stand out from the crowd with bold, vibrant lash sets your clients will love. Designed for lash technicians who want to offer something truly unique. ✦ 6 vivid colors per tray — blue, green, purple, red, pink &amp; violet ✦ Available in C &amp; D curl | 0.07mm thickness | 10–13mm lengths ✦ Up to 4,000 lashes per tray — maximum value per palette ✦ High-quality synthetic fiber — even, elastic, shape-retaining ✦ Tested by Lovely&apos;s quality department for consistent performance Who It&apos;s For Perfect for lash artists offering color sets, special occasion looks, or clients who want to express their personality through their lashes. Quality You Can Trust Each tray is rigorously tested to ensure lashes don&apos;t deform during application and hold their shape throughout wear.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4632682397747</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Colored Eyelash Extensions, colorful eyelash extensions, colorful lashes, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, lashes</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">CREATIVE-6LINES-C-007-10MM, CREATIVE-6LINES-C-007-11MM, CREATIVE-6LINES-C-007-12MM, CREATIVE-6LINES-C-007-13MM, CREATIVE-6LINES-D-007-10MM, CREATIVE-6LINES-D-007-11MM, CREATIVE-6LINES-D-007-12MM, CREATIVE-6LINES-D-007-13MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">8</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4632675582003" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/creative-eyelash-extensions-20-lines-1</url>
        <price>13</price>
        <oldprice>20</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1238_8bcab3a7-79af-40cb-8978-943d98083e25.jpg?v=1762457189</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9905-2.jpg?v=1603487127</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9906.jpg?v=1603487131</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1259.jpg?v=1597363597</picture>
        <name>Creative Eyelash Extensions | 20 Lines | Salut | C D Curl | 0.07 | 10–14mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>CREATIVE-C-007-10MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Unleash Your Creativity with Salut Colored Lash Extensions Designed for lash artists who dare to go beyond black, the Salut 20-Line Tray by Lovely US delivers a full spectrum of vivid, salon-quality color in one stunning palette. Whether you&apos;re adding a pop of color to a classic set or creating a fully vibrant look, Salut gives you the freedom to express it all. 15 Vibrant Colors in Every Tray Each tray includes: white, yellow, orange, burgundy, red, pink, fuchsia, cornflower blue, purple, blue, azure, emerald green, blue-green, yellow-green, and green — perfect for mixing, layering, and creating one-of-a-kind lash art your clients will rave about. Why Lash Techs Love Salut Up to 13,000 lashes per tray — maximum value, minimum restocking 20 lines per palette — organized, easy to work from during appointments Premium high-quality fiber — perfectly even, elastic, and shape-retaining No deformation — lashes hold their curl and structure throughout wear Versatile use — apply as the main color or as accent lashes within black/brown sets Quality You Can Trust Every Salut palette is rigorously tested by the Lovely Lash quality department. Made from premium synthetic fiber, these lashes are engineered for professional application — consistent, reliable, and beautiful every time. Exceptional Value for Professionals We believe your clients deserve high-end results without breaking your budget. That&apos;s why Lovely US brings you 20-line trays at prices that make sense for your business — so you can keep clients coming back and your margins healthy.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4632675582003</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">20 line lash tray, Colored Eyelash Extensions, colored lash extensions, colored lashes, colorful eyelash extensions, colorful lash extensions, colorful lashes, Creative eyelash extensions, creative lash tray, creative lashes, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lash artist supplies, lash extension tray, lashes, Lovely US lashes, professional lash supplies, Salut lashes</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">CREATIVE-C-007-10MM, CREATIVE-C-007-11MM, CREATIVE-C-007-12MM, CREATIVE-C-007-13MM, CREATIVE-C-007-14MM, CREATIVE-D-007-10MM, CREATIVE-D-007-11MM, CREATIVE-D-007-12MM, CREATIVE-D-007-13MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">9</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4632656478259" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/creative-eyelash-extensions-20-lines</url>
        <price>11</price>
        <oldprice>20</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1288_ec05e674-e120-4b02-82fc-70af3e52d734.jpg?v=1762457189</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9938.jpg?v=1603487203</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9939.jpg?v=1603487209</picture>
        <name>Creative Eyelash Extensions | 20 Lines | Pastel | C D Curl | 0.07 | 10–13mm</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>PASTEL-C-007-10MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Turn every set into a work of art. Lovely&apos;s Pastel Creative Eyelash Extensions give lash technicians a full spectrum of expression — each 20-line tray includes 6 hand-curated colors: Fuchsia, Lilac, Turquoise, Emerald, Sea Azure, and Cornflower . Use them as bold statement lashes, subtle color accents alongside classic black or brown sets, or mix shades to craft one-of-a-kind looks your clients will rave about. Why Lash Techs Love These 20 lines per tray — up to 13,000 lashes depending on thickness, so you get maximum value per palette Premium fiber — perfectly uniform, elastic, and shape-retaining through the full wear cycle Versatile application — works as a primary color or accent; mix freely for custom creative looks Rigorously tested — every palette passes Lovely&apos;s in-house quality control before it ships Built for Professionals Lovely is trusted by 5,000+ lash professionals across North America and tens of thousands worldwide. We design every product to help you deliver high-end results at prices that protect your margins — because your clients deserve beautiful, and so does your business.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4632656478259</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Colored Eyelash Extensions, colored lashes, colorful eyelash extensions, colorful lashes, Creative eyelash extensions, creative lashes, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">PASTEL-C-007-10MM, PASTEL-C-007-11MM, PASTEL-C-007-12MM, PASTEL-C-007-13MM, PASTEL-D-007-10MM, PASTEL-D-007-11MM, PASTEL-D-007-12MM, PASTEL-D-007-13MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">8</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4632538906675" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/ideal-eyelash-extensions-20-lines-mix</url>
        <price>20</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions.jpg?v=1762457187</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-0081.jpg?v=1603918528</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9829copy.jpg?v=1603489320</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart2_6ce817d9-f027-4cc5-a890-fd352cf3bc57.jpg?v=1597504806</picture>
        <name>Ideal Eyelash Extensions | 20 Lines | MIX | Black | B C C+ CC D L L+ M Curl | 0.05–0.15 | 7–15mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEAL-B-007-7-15MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Complete 20 Line Mix Eyelash Extensions for Every Lash Design Streamline your lash inventory with our Ideal Eyelash Extensions 20 Line Mix – the all-in-one solution for professional lash artists who need multiple lengths in one convenient tray. Why Lash Technicians Choose the 20 Line Mix Complete Length Range: Mixed lengths in one tray for creating seamless lash maps without switching between multiple trays 20 Lines of Variety: Professional assortment designed for maximum efficiency and creative flexibility Time-Saving Convenience: Everything you need for classic, hybrid, and volume sets in one organized tray Premium Quality Fibers: Soft, lightweight lashes with natural shine and superior retention Consistent Curl Pattern: Uniform curl across all lengths for predictable, beautiful results every time Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Perfect for Busy Lash Artists Designed to simplify your workflow while maintaining the highest quality standards. Create custom lash designs efficiently with all the lengths you need at your fingertips. Work smarter, not harder. The 20 Line Mix gives you professional versatility without the clutter of multiple trays.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4632538906675</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Classic Eyelash Extensions, Classic Lashes, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, Ideal Lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, lashes, Lovely US Lashes, Volume eyelash extensions, Volume Lashes</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">B, C, C+, CC, D, M, L, L+</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10, 0.15, 0.05, 0.12</param>
        <param name="Size" noFilter="true">7-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEAL-B-007-7-15MM, IDEAL-B-010-7-15MM, IDEAL-C-007-7-15MM, IDEAL-C-010-7-15MM, IDEAL-C-015-7-15MM, IDEAL-C+-005-7-15MM, IDEAL-C+-007-7-15MM, IDEAL-C+-010-7-15MM, IDEAL-C+-012-7-15MM, IDEAL-CC-005-7-15MM, IDEAL-CC-007-7-15MM, IDEAL-D-007-7-15MM, IDEAL-D-010-7-15MM, IDEAL-D-012-7-15MM, IDEAL-M-005-7-15MM, IDEAL-M-007-7-15MM, IDEAL-M-010-7-15MM, IDEAL-L-007-7-15MM, IDEAL-L-010-7-15MM, IDEAL-L+-010-7-15MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">20</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4632507908147" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/ideal-eyelash-extensions-20-lines</url>
        <price>20</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_9fc40197-92fc-4b18-be4f-ac641eff76b7.jpg?v=1762457187</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_c8143654-e2c6-417d-8b62-8039bae8de03.jpg?v=1656021301</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart2.jpg?v=1656021272</picture>
        <name>Ideal Eyelash Extensions | 20 Lines | Black | C D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 &amp; 0.15 | 7–20mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>IDEAL-C-007-7MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Classic 20 Line Eyelash Extensions for Professional Lash Artists Elevate your lash artistry with our Ideal Eyelash Extensions - 20 Lines , the foundation of every professional lash artist&apos;s toolkit. Designed for consistent, beautiful results across all lash techniques. Why Professionals Trust Ideal Extensions 20 Lines of Premium Lashes: Full professional tray with up to 13,000 high-quality extensions for multiple client applications Versatile Curl Options: Available in multiple curl types to suit every client&apos;s eye shape and desired look Superior Quality Fibers: Soft, lightweight synthetic lashes with a natural matte finish and excellent retention Consistent Performance: Reliable curl memory and flexibility for seamless application every time Multi-Technique Ready: Perfect for classic sets, hybrid designs, and volume fan creation Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Professional-Grade Quality Each lash is precision-manufactured to meet the exacting standards of professional lash technicians. From natural everyday looks to dramatic evening styles, these extensions deliver flawless results that keep clients satisfied. The professional standard for lash extensions. Build your reputation on quality that performs appointment after appointment.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4632507908147</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, Ideal Eyelash Extensions, Ideal lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely Lashes</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10, 0.15</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">7mm, 8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 14mm, 17mm, 18mm, 19mm, 20mm, 15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">IDEAL-C-007-7MM, IDEAL-C-007-8MM, IDEAL-C-007-9MM, IDEAL-C-007-10MM, IDEAL-C-007-11MM, IDEAL-C-007-12MM, IDEAL-C-007-13MM, IDEAL-C-007-14MM, IDEAL-C-007-17MM, IDEAL-C-007-18MM, IDEAL-C-007-19MM, IDEAL-C-007-20MM, IDEAL-C-010-7MM, IDEAL-C-010-8MM, IDEAL-C-010-9MM, IDEAL-C-010-10MM, IDEAL-C-010-11MM, IDEAL-C-010-12MM, IDEAL-C-010-13MM, IDEAL-C-010-17MM, +28 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">48</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="4632493654067" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/3d-4d-5d-6d-elite-eyelash-extensions-12-lines</url>
        <price>12</price>
        <oldprice>18</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1210.jpg?v=1762457186</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9921.jpg?v=1603486862</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9920.jpg?v=1603486857</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9918.jpg?v=1603486853</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_US_Eyelash_Extensions-1359.jpg?v=1597506531</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_US_Eyelash_Extensions-1358.jpg?v=1597506561</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_US_Eyelash_Extensions-1357.jpg?v=1597506596</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely_US_Eyelash_Extensions-1355.jpg?v=1597506609</picture>
        <name>Elite Premade Fans Eyelash Extensions | 12 Lines | MIX | Black | C C+ CC D Curl | 0.05 &amp; 0.07 | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely US</vendor>
        <vendorCode>EFANS-3D-C-005</vendorCode>
        <description>Elite Premade Fan Eyelash Extensions – 12 Lines | 3D, 4D, 5D &amp; 6D Take your volume work to the next level with Elite Eyelash Extensions — precision-crafted premade fans designed for volume and mega volume sets. Each fan features an ultra-thin base that dramatically reduces application time while delivering flawless, full results your clients will love. Why Professionals Choose Elite Fans Premade Fan Design: Ultra-thin base for faster application and seamless bonding — no hand-fanning required 12 Lines Per Tray: Packed with high-quality extensions for multiple client applications 3D, 4D, 5D &amp; 6D Options: Choose your fan density to match any client&apos;s desired volume level Lightweight &amp; Elastic: Soft, high-quality synthetic fiber that holds its curl and shape throughout wear Multi-Curl Available: C, C+, CC, and D curls to suit every eye shape and style preference Fan Guide 3D: Light, natural-looking volume — great for first-time volume clients 4D: Medium volume for a fuller, defined look 5D: Full volume for a glamorous, dramatic effect 6D: Mega volume for maximum fullness and impact Thickness Guide 0.05: Ultra-fine — ideal for mega volume and sensitive natural lashes 0.07: Fine — most popular for volume sets Professional-Grade Quality Every tray is thoroughly tested by the Lovely US quality department. Elite fans are precision-manufactured to meet the exacting standards of professional lash technicians — delivering consistent curl memory, flexibility, and retention appointment after appointment. The professional standard for volume lash extensions. Save time, elevate results, and keep clients coming back.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">4632493654067</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">3D Eyelash Extensions, 3D Lashes, 4D Eyelash Extensions, 4D lashes, 5D Eyelash Extensions, 5D lashes, 6D eyelash Extensions, 6D lashes, Eyelash Extensions, eyelashes, False Eyelash Extensions, Individual Eyelash Extensions, Lash Fans, lashes, Lovely US Eyelash Extensions, Pre made Fans Eyelash Extensions, Volume Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Fan" noFilter="true">3D, 4D, 5D, 6D</param>
        <param name="Curl" noFilter="true">C, D, C+, CC</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.05, 0.07</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">EFANS-3D-C-005, EFANS-3D-D-005, EFANS-4D-C-005, EFANS-4D-D-005, EFANS-5D-C-005, EFANS-5D-D-005, EFANS-5D-C+-007, EFANS-5D-CC-005, EFANS-6D-C-005, EFANS-6D-C-007, EFANS-6D-D-005, EFANS-6D-D-007, EFANS-6D-C+-005, EFANS-6D-CC-005, EFANS-3D-D-007</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">15</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="3870583390275" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/lovely-black-eyelash-extensions-royal-lashes-16-lines-mix</url>
        <price>17</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1384_1ef5686b-9bbe-4d70-b104-20cdf9b893b5.jpg?v=1762457138</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9929_337eb243-71a9-41f7-adab-a4860c9f4a72.jpg?v=1603487928</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart_51852d11-bbe0-4d81-b2f4-b3d748f76909.jpg?v=1597504635</picture>
        <name>Royal Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | MIX | Black | B C C+ CC D L L+ M Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 &amp; 0.12 | 7–15mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ROYAL-B-007-7-15MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Premium Royal Eyelash Extensions - 16 Line MIX Transform your lash artistry with our professional-grade Royal Eyelash Extensions. This 16-line mixed tray delivers exceptional versatility for creating customized, dimensional lash looks that keep clients coming back. Why Lash Artists Choose Royal Extensions Mixed Length Variety: Perfect assortment for volume and hybrid sets, allowing seamless blending and natural-to-dramatic styling Superior Retention: Premium synthetic fibers hold their curl and maintain flawless appearance for weeks Effortless Application: Consistent thickness and easy-release strips speed up your lash mapping process Professional Results: Deep black color creates bold, defined lashes without mascara 16 Organized Lines: Efficient tray layout keeps your workspace organized during appointments What&apos;s Included In this 16 line tray there are up to 10,500 lashes depending on their thickness. Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Technical Specifications Each tray contains carefully curated mixed lengths ideal for creating texture, dimension, and customized lash designs. The ultra-fine base ensures comfortable wear and invisible bonds. Perfect for: Volume sets, hybrid techniques, mega volume applications, and creative lash mapping Trusted by professional lash technicians across North America for consistent quality and reliable performance. Elevate every client&apos;s lash experience with Royal Extensions.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">3870583390275</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Classic Eyelash Extensions, eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, lashes, Royal Eyelash Extensions, Royal Lashes, Volume eyelash extensions</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">B, C, C+, CC, D, M, L, L+</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10, 0.12</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">7-15mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ROYAL-B-007-7-15MM, ROYAL-B-010-7-15MM, ROYAL-C-007-7-15MM, ROYAL-C-010-7-15MM, ROYAL-C+-007-7-15MM, ROYAL-C+-010-7-15MM, ROYAL-C+-012-7-15MM, ROYAL-CC-007-7-15MM, ROYAL-CC-010-7-15MM, ROYAL-D-007-7-15MM, ROYAL-D-010-7-15MM, ROYAL-D-012-7-15MM, ROYAL-M-007-7-15MM, ROYAL-M-010-7-15MM, ROYAL-L-007-7-15MM, ROYAL-L-010-7-15MM, ROYAL-L+-007-7-15MM, ROYAL-L+-010-7-15MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">18</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="3870520279107" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/lovely-black-eyelash-extensions-royal-lashes-16-lines</url>
        <price>17</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>3</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-1384_5fc43533-17e1-4ad1-aaef-faf70ffbfe14.jpg?v=1762457136</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9926.jpg?v=1603487854</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSEyelashExtensions-9929.jpg?v=1603487859</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/LovelyUSLashChart.jpg?v=1597504571</picture>
        <name>Royal Eyelash Extensions | 16 Lines | Black | C D Curl | 0.07 &amp; 0.10 &amp; 0.12 &amp; 0.15 | 8–16mm | Lovely</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Extensions</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>ROYAL-C-007-8MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Royal Eyelash Extensions - Professional 16 Line Tray Deliver flawless lash applications every time with our Royal Eyelash Extensions. This professional 16-line tray is the foundation of exceptional lash artistry, offering premium quality fibers that professional lash technicians depend on for stunning, long-lasting results. Professional-Grade Quality Consistent Perfection: Every lash maintains uniform thickness, taper, and curl for seamless application and beautiful symmetry Superior Retention: Advanced fiber technology ensures extensions stay put for 4-6 weeks with proper aftercare Rich Black Pigment: Deep, true black color eliminates the need for mascara and creates dramatic definition Lightweight Comfort: Ultra-fine construction feels natural and weightless on clients&apos; eyes Organized Efficiency: 16-line tray layout streamlines your workflow and reduces appointment time What&apos;s Included In this 16 line tray there are up to 10,500 lashes depending on their thickness. Length Guide 8mm-9mm: Used on the inside &amp; outside of the eye area 10mm-12mm: Most commonly used for the middle of eye for a natural look 13mm and 14mm: Creates a bold look 15mm and 16mm: Very bold length, should not be used unless the natural lashes are strong Thickness Guide .07: Most popular for volume .10: Used for volume .12: Thin classic lash .15: A medium classic diameter .18: A good average thickness for classic .20: Used for classic dramatic look Versatile Application Ideal for classic lash sets, these extensions work beautifully across all eye shapes and natural lash types. Whether you&apos;re creating natural enhancement or bold glamour, Royal Extensions deliver the precision and quality your artistry deserves. Technical Excellence: Easy-release strips, consistent curl retention, flexible yet durable fibers, and professional-grade adhesion compatibility. Trusted by lash artists throughout North America. Stock your station with the extensions that elevate your reputation and keep clients loyal.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">3870520279107</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelashes, eyelashes extensions, False Eyelash Extensions, False lashes, individual eyelash extensions, Individual lash extensions, Individual Lashes, lashes, Lovely US Lashes, Royal Eyelash Extensions</param>
        <param name="Bend" noFilter="true">C, D</param>
        <param name="Thickness" noFilter="true">0.07, 0.10, 0.12, 0.15</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">8mm, 9mm, 10mm, 11mm, 12mm, 13mm, 7mm, 14mm, 15mm, 16mm</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">ROYAL-C-007-8MM, ROYAL-C-007-9MM, ROYAL-C-007-10MM, ROYAL-C-007-11MM, ROYAL-C-007-12MM, ROYAL-C-007-13MM, ROYAL-C-010-7MM, ROYAL-C-010-8MM, ROYAL-C-010-9MM, ROYAL-C-010-10MM, ROYAL-C-010-11MM, ROYAL-C-012-10MM, ROYAL-C-015-10MM, ROYAL-C-015-11MM, ROYAL-D-007-8MM, ROYAL-D-007-9MM, ROYAL-D-007-10MM, ROYAL-D-007-11MM, ROYAL-D-007-12MM, ROYAL-D-007-13MM, +19 more</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">39</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1682880921667" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/micro-brushes</url>
        <price>5</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>7</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/image_a69c1828-5ca0-4416-acee-51d900a27587.jpg?v=1776786577</picture>
        <name>Micro Brushes</name>
        <typePrefix>Related Materials</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>MICRO-BRUSHES-SMALL</vendorCode>
        <description>These micro brushes are used in degreasing and removing eyelashes. Use very little preparation gels and creams, unlike cotton swabs. Quality lint of micro brushes does not peel or abrade during use. 100 per pack 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed For over 8 years we have been bringing you the most professional products at affordable prices Brand One of the largest beauty brands worldwide we have over 5,000+ customers in North America and tens of thousands around the world. Our mission is to help you Enhance Beauty where you are. Shipping Orders are processed and shipped SAME DAY on all orders placed before 1pm Eastern Time Mon-Fri. Free Shipping in US on Orders over $100.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1682880921667</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Related Materials</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelash extension micro brushes, eyelash micro brushes, lash micro brushes, Micro Brushes</param>
        <param name="Size" noFilter="true">Small, Medium, Large</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">MICRO-BRUSHES-SMALL, MICRO-BRUSHES-MEDIUM, MICRO-BRUSHES-LARGE</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">3</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1642623533123" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/remover-cream-caramel-scented</url>
        <price>17</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>6</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/image_f94ef4df-a32d-40b5-b23d-468adf1fe188.jpg?v=1762457126</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Cream_-_Remover_Lovely_Caramel_-1.jpg?v=1687907591</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely-05165.jpg?v=1687907591</picture>
        <name>Cream Remover - Caramel Scented</name>
        <typePrefix>Preparations</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>CREAM-REMOVER-CARAMEL-15G</vendorCode>
        <description>Cream Remover – Caramel Scented Gentle, Fast-Acting Lash Extension Remover for Professional Use The Cream Remover – Caramel Scented is a professional-grade lash extension remover designed for easy, quick, and comfortable removal. Its smooth cream formula dissolves adhesive bonds efficiently without lumps or burning sensation, leaving natural lashes clean and undamaged. Enjoy the pleasant caramel scent while delivering a spa-like experience for your clients. Why Lash Artists Choose This Remover Fast-acting formula – Dissolves lash adhesive quickly for efficient removal sessions Gentle on natural lashes – No burning sensation or irritation during removal Smooth cream consistency – Easy to apply with a micro brush for precise placement Pleasant caramel scent – Elevates the client experience with a spa-like aroma Lump-free results – Clean removal every time with no residue Professional-grade quality – Refined over 8+ years for safe, reliable performance Application Instructions Using a micro brush, take a small amount of the cream remover Evenly apply onto the surface of the lash extensions, focusing on the bond points where artificial lashes meet natural lashes Leave on for a few minutes to allow the formula to dissolve the adhesive Carefully remove with a cotton pad Rinse lashes thoroughly with water, using a facial cleanser if needed Shelf Life &amp; Storage Shelf life: 2 years from production date (unopened) After opening: Use within 6 months for optimal performance Store in a cool, dark place away from direct sunlight and heat Ingredients Propylene Carbonate, Montmorillonite, Fragrance Storage &amp; Safety Store in a cool, dark place away from direct sunlight and heat Keep container tightly sealed when not in use For professional external use only – suitable for individual eyelash extension removal Avoid contact with eyes; if contact occurs, rinse with warm water and seek medical attention Keep out of reach of children Why Choose Lovely US We&apos;re one of the largest professional lash brands worldwide, trusted by over 5,000+ lash artists in North America and tens of thousands globally. Our formulas have been perfected over 8+ years to bring you the safest and highest quality products. We&apos;re committed to helping you enhance beauty wherever you are. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed – We stand behind the quality of every product we create.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1642623533123</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Preparations</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelash extensions remover cream, eyelash remover cream, lash remover cream</param>
        <param name="Expiration date" noFilter="true">11/05/2027</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">CREAM-REMOVER-CARAMEL-15G</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1642549837891" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/primer-without-perfume</url>
        <price>12</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>6</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Lovely-9567.jpg?v=1776786577</picture>
        <name>Primer - Without Scent</name>
        <typePrefix>Preparations</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>PRIMER-NO-SCENT</vendorCode>
        <description>This primer is designed for people sensitive to scent. It increases the duration of eyelash wear for 1-2 weeks. Primer has light evaporation. Apply a small amount of the product to the micro brush and wipe the eyelashes. Avoid primer on the skin. Precaution Avoid contact with eyes. In case of contact, rinse thoroughly with water; consult a doctor if necessary. Shelf Life 2 years | 6 months after opening | Store in cool dry place Value Over the last 8 years we have fine tuned and perfected all of our formulas bringing you the safest and highest quality products. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed Each palette of eyelashes is thoroughly tested by Lovely Lash quality department. Lovely eyelash extensions are made of a high-quality fiber, perfectly even and elastic. Eyelashes do not deform in the process of extension and perfectly hold their shape while wearing. Brand One of the largest beauty brands worldwide we have over 5,000+ customers in North America and tens of thousands around the world. Our mission is to help you Enhance Beauty where you are. Shipping Orders are processed and shipped SAME DAY on all orders placed before 1pm Eastern Time Mon-Fri. Free Shipping in US on Orders over $100.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1642549837891</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Preparations</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelash extensions primer, lash primer, primer</param>
        <param name="Expiration date" noFilter="true">02/20/2028</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">PRIMER-NO-SCENT</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1642481483843" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/remover-cream-sensitive</url>
        <price>15</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>6</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/files/image_d6426c3d-f5d6-47a2-aa2e-f778b3f530f7.jpg?v=1776786577</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Cream-Remover_Lovely_Sensitive.jpg?v=1687907753</picture>
        <name>Cream Remover - Sensitive</name>
        <typePrefix>Preparations</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>CREAM-REMOVER-NO-SCENT</vendorCode>
        <description>Cream Remover – Sensitive Formulated for the most delicate clients, our Cream Remover for Sensitive Eyes dissolves lash extension adhesive gently and completely — no tugging, no irritation, no compromise on results. Its light, non-drip cream consistency gives you full control during application, making it the go-to choice for lash techs who prioritize both precision and client comfort. Key Benefits: Gentle on sensitive eyes – safe for even the most reactive clients Light cream consistency – easy to apply with a micro brush, no mess Fast-acting formula – effectively dissolves adhesive bonds in minutes Clean removal – leaves natural lashes intact and residue-free Professional-grade performance – trusted by lash artists worldwide Perfect For: Lash techs working with sensitive or reactive clients Professionals who need a reliable, controlled removal process Salons committed to the highest standards of client care and safety How to Use: Using a micro brush, take a small amount and apply evenly along the lash line, focusing on the bonding points. Leave on for a few minutes, then gently remove with a cotton pad. Rinse lashes with water and follow with a gentle cleanser if needed. Shelf life: 2 years | After opening: Use within 6 months | Storage: Keep in a cool, dark place Ingredients: Propylene Carbonate, Montmorillonite Pro Tip: For best results, apply in a thin, even layer and avoid contact with the skin. Always perform a patch test on new or highly sensitive clients before full application.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1642481483843</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Preparations</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">eyelash extensions remover cream, eyelash remover cream, lash remover cream, remover cream, sensitive eyelash remover cream</param>
        <param name="Expiration date" noFilter="true">11/05/2027</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">CREAM-REMOVER-NO-SCENT</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1641911091267" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/straight-tweezers-for-eyelash-extensions</url>
        <price>16.99</price>
        <oldprice>19.99</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_6fc7b744-bcdb-49e5-9cfe-328cad0747f9.jpg?v=1762457122</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Straight_Tweezers.png?v=1603895898</picture>
        <name>Eyelash Extension Tweezers - Straight</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-STRAIGHT-STIFF-OG</vendorCode>
        <description>Straight Isolation Tweezers Most suitable for comfortably isolating eyelashes. The essential tweezers all eyelash masters must have. Can be used for picking up lashes for classic sets. All Lovely Tweezers are hand sharpened and made of the highest quality. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed Over the last 8 years we have fine tuned and perfected the lashing process to bring you the safest highest quality products to make your lashing process faster and smoother leading to better results and more repeat clients. Brand One of the largest beauty brands worldwide we have over 5,000+ customers in North America and tens of thousands around the world. Our mission is to help you Enhance Beauty where you are. Shipping Orders are processed and shipped SAME DAY on all orders placed before 1pm Eastern Time Mon-Fri. Free Shipping in US on Orders over $100.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1641911091267</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers, Lash Tweezers, Tweezers, Tweezers for eyelash extensions</param>
        <param name="Stiffness" noFilter="true">Stiff Hold</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-STRAIGHT-STIFF-OG</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">1</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1641891233859" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/tweezers-for-eyelash-extensions-curved</url>
        <price>16.99</price>
        <oldprice>19.99</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_964dd390-8ec4-4b3f-9ec7-243044994e5b.jpg?v=1762457121</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Curved_Tweezers.png?v=1603895786</picture>
        <name>Eyelash Extension Tweezers - Curved</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-OG-CURVED-STIFF</vendorCode>
        <description>Curved Isolation Tweezers Most suitable for comfortably isolating eyelashes. The curved tip allows you to isolate eyelashes without resting/touching the brow bone. Can be used for picking up lashes for classic sets or light volume sets. All Lovely Tweezers are hand sharpened and made of the highest quality. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed Over the last 8 years we have fine tuned and perfected the lashing process to bring you the safest highest quality products to make your lashing process faster and smoother leading to better results and more repeat clients. Brand One of the largest beauty brands worldwide we have over 5,000+ customers in North America and tens of thousands around the world. Our mission is to help you Enhance Beauty where you are. Shipping Orders are processed and shipped SAME DAY on all orders placed before 1pm Eastern Time Mon-Fri. Free Shipping in US on Orders over $100.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1641891233859</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers, Lash Tweezers, Tweezers, Tweezers for eyelash extensions</param>
        <param name="Stiffness" noFilter="true">Stiff Hold, Soft Hold</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-OG-CURVED-STIFF, TWZ-OG-CURVED-SOFT</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">2</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1641844998211" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/boot-tweezers-for-eyelashes</url>
        <price>15.99</price>
        <oldprice>19.99</oldprice>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_586c5a48-ab0b-4399-adfd-2f625f140ed2.jpg?v=1762457120</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/Boot_Tweezers.png?v=1603895731</picture>
        <name>Eyelash Extension Tweezers - Boot (L-Straight)</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-OG-L-STRAIGHT-STIFF</vendorCode>
        <description>Boot Volume Tweezers Most suitable for volume sets, to effortlessly create fans, and have ease of placement for volume or mega volume lashes. All Lovely Tweezers are hand sharpened and made of the highest quality. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed Over the last 8 years we have fine tuned and perfected the lashing process to bring you the safest highest quality products to make your lashing process faster and smoother leading to better results and more repeat clients. Brand One of the largest beauty brands worldwide we have over 5,000+ customers in North America and tens of thousands around the world. Our mission is to help you Enhance Beauty where you are. Shipping Orders are processed and shipped SAME DAY on all orders placed before 1pm Eastern Time Mon-Fri. Free Shipping in US on Orders over $100.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1641844998211</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers, Lash Tweezers, Tweezers, Tweezers for eyelash extensions</param>
        <param name="Stiffness" noFilter="true">Stiff Hold, Soft Hold</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-OG-L-STRAIGHT-STIFF, TWZ-OG-L-STRAIGHT-SOFT</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">2</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1641823469635" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/tweezers-for-eyelash-extensions-type-g</url>
        <price>19.99</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image_b25d3d20-0491-45bf-9f88-82b94c6a29ae.jpg?v=1762457119</picture>
        <name>Eyelash Extension Tweezers - 90°</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-OG-90-STIFF-5MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Classic | Volume Tweezers Most suitable for classic and light volume sets pick up. All Lovely Tweezers are hand sharpened and made of the highest quality. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed Over the last 8 years we have fine tuned and perfected the lashing process to bring you the safest highest quality products to make your lashing process faster and smoother leading to better results and more repeat clients. Brand One of the largest beauty brands worldwide we have over 5,000+ customers in North America and tens of thousands around the world. Our mission is to help you Enhance Beauty where you are. Shipping Orders are processed and shipped SAME DAY on all orders placed before 1pm Eastern Time Mon-Fri. Free Shipping in US on Orders over $100.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1641823469635</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers, lash tweezers, Tweezers, Tweezers for eyelash extensions</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">5mm, 7mm</param>
        <param name="Type" noFilter="true">Stiff Hold, Soft Hold</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-OG-90-STIFF-5MM, TWZ-OG-90-STIFF-7MM, TWZ-OG-90-SOFT-5MM, TWZ-OG-90-SOFT-7MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">4</param>
      </offer>
      <offer id="1641705439299" available="true">
        <url>https://lovelyus.com/products/lovely-tweezers-for-volume-eyelash-extensions</url>
        <price>19.99</price>
        <currencyId>USD</currencyId>
        <categoryId>4</categoryId>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/image.jpg?v=1762457119</picture>
        <picture>https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0057/6625/0563/products/L_Tweezers.png?v=1603895604</picture>
        <name>Eyelash Extension Tweezers - 45°</name>
        <typePrefix>Eyelash Tweezers</typePrefix>
        <vendor>Lovely</vendor>
        <vendorCode>TWZ-OG-45-STIFF-5MM</vendorCode>
        <description>Classic | Light Volume Tweezers Most suitable for comfortably picking up lashes for classic and light volume sets or eyelash isolation. All Lovely Tweezers are hand sharpened and made of the highest quality. 100% Satisfaction Guaranteed Over the last 8 years we have fine tuned and perfected the lashing process to bring you the safest highest quality products to make your lashing process faster and smoother leading to better results and more repeat clients. Brand One of the largest beauty brands worldwide we have over 5,000+ customers in North America and tens of thousands around the world. Our mission is to help you Enhance Beauty where you are. Shipping Orders are processed and shipped SAME DAY on all orders placed before 1pm Eastern Time Mon-Fri. Free Shipping in US on Orders over $100.</description>
        <param name="Shopify ID" noFilter="true">1641705439299</param>
        <param name="Product Type" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers</param>
        <param name="Tags" noFilter="true">Eyelash Tweezers, Lash Tweezers, Tweezers, Tweezers for eyelash extensions</param>
        <param name="Length" noFilter="true">5mm, 7mm</param>
        <param name="Stiffness" noFilter="true">Stiff Hold, Soft Hold</param>
        <param name="SKU" noFilter="true">TWZ-OG-45-STIFF-5MM, TWZ-OG-45-STIFF-7MM, TWZ-OG-45-SOFT-5MM, TWZ-OG-45-SOFT-7MM</param>
        <param name="Variants Count" noFilter="true">4</param>
      </offer>
    </offers>
  </shop>
</yml_catalog>
